난 어떻게 죽을지 생각해
본 적은 없었지만
I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
사랑하는 사람이 있는 곳에서
죽는 것은 괜찮은 방법같다
But dying in the place of someone I love
seems like a good way to go.
(WINGS FLUTTERING)
(OMINOUS THEME PLAYING)
그러니 집을 떠난 결정을
후회할 수 없다
BELLA: So I can't bring myself
to regret the decision to leave home.
피닉스가 그리울 것이다
I would miss Phoenix.
날씨도 그립고
I'd miss the heat.
사랑스럽고 별나고 자상한
엄마도 그립다
I would miss my loving, erratic,
harebrained mother.
알았다
(SOFTLY) Okay.
- 르네, 빨리와
새아빠도
PHIL: Renee, come on.
BELLA: And her new husband.
둘 다 사랑하지만
비행기 타러 가야지
Guys, come on. I love you both.
We got a plane to catch.
두 분이 여행을 가게돼서
아빠와 지내기로 했다
But they want to go on the road,
so I'm gonna spend some time with my dad,
잘 한 거 같다
and this will be a good thing.
내 생각엔
I think.
When the thorn bush turns white
(SINGING) When the thorn bush turns white
That's when I'll come home
I am going out to see what I can sow
And I don't know where I'll go
And I don't know what I'll see
워싱턴 주에서
BELLA: In the state of Washington,
끊임없이 내리는 비를
뚫고 가다보면
under a near constant cover
of clouds and rain,
포크스라는 작은 마을이 있다
there's a small town named Forks.
주민수 3120명이고
Population, 3120 people.
이곳으로 이사간다
This is where I'm moving.
우리 아빠 찰리이다
My dad's Charlie.
경찰서장이시다
He's the chief of police.
Curse the powers that be
Cause all I want is...
머리가 길어졌구나
Your hair's longer.
지난번 만난 후에 잘랐어요
I cut it since the last time I saw you.
또 자랐나보구나
Guess it grew out again.
매년 여름 2주간
여기서 지냈다
BELLA: I used to spend two weeks here
almost every summer,
하지만 1년만에 왔다
but it's been years.
화장실 선반 비워뒀다
I've cleared some shelves off
in the bathroom.
그렇지, 화장실 하나죠
Right. One bathroom.
좋은 전등이야
It's a pretty good work lamp.
판매직원이 침대보를 골라줬다
The sales lady picked out the bed stuff.
너 보라색 좋아하지?
You like purple, right?
보라색 괜찮아요
Purple's cool.
고마워요
Thanks.
그래
Okay.
아빠의 좋은 점 하나는
BELLA: One of the best things about Charlie,
혼자 놔둔다는 거다
he doesn't hover.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
여기까지 와줬군
Heard you guys coming
all the way down the road.
반갑네
Good to see you.
- 벨라, 빌리 블랙씨 기억하지?
- 네
- Bella, you remember Billy Black.
- Yeah.
- 멋져 보이세요
- 아직도 한창이지
- Wow, you're looking good.
- Well, I'm still dancing.
네가 와서 기쁘구나
I'm glad you're finally here.
너 온다고 아빠가 입을
다물지를 않더라
Charlie here hasn't shut up about it
since you told him you were coming.
(CHUCKLES)
계속 뻥치면 진흙속에
밀어버리겠어
All right, keep exaggerating.
I'll roll you into the mud.
발목을 받아버릴까
After I ram you in the ankles.
- 한번 해볼텐가?
- 그래
- CHARLIE: You want to go?
- Yeah.
덤벼봐!
Bring it.
- 안녕, 난 제이콥이야
- 그래
- Hi, I'm Jacob.
- Hey.
우리 어릴 때 진흙
장난하고 그랬지
We used to make mud pies
when we were little.
맞아, 기억나
Right. No, I remember.
(LAUGHS)
두 분 늘 저래?
Are they always like this?
- 나이 드시면서 더 나빠지지
- 그렇군
- It's getting worse with old age.
- Good.
그래 어떠니?
So, what do you think?
뭐가요?
Of what?
- 네 귀향 선물
- 이 차요?
- Your homecoming present.
- This?
- 빌리에게 샀지
- 그래
- Just bought it off Billy here.
- Yep.
- 내가 엔진을 다시 조립했어
- 이럴수가
- I totally rebuilt the engine for you.
- Come on.
세상에!
Oh, my gosh!
이거 완벽해요! 정말이죠?
This is perfect. Are you joking me?
(JACOB GRUNTS)
미안
Sorry.
좋아할 거라고 했지
I told you she'd love it.
애들을 잘 알거든
I'm down with the kids.
그래, 자넨 꽝이야
Oh, yeah, dude. You're the bomb.
좋았어
Okay.
변속할 때 클러치를
두 번 밟아야하지만
Listen, you gotta double-pump
the clutch when you shift,
그 외에는 괜찮아
but besides that, you should be good.
- 이거 말야?
- 그래, 거기
- That's this one?
- Yeah. Yeah, right there.
알았어
All right.
학교에 태워다줄까?
Do you want a ride to school or something?
난 인디언학교 다녀
I go to school on the reservation.
- 그렇구나
- 그래
- Right, right.
- Yeah.
아쉽네, 아는 사람이
있으면 좋았을텐데
That's too bad.
It would've been nice to know one person.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
새 학교에서의 첫날은
BELLA: My first day at a new school.
3월, 학기 중간이었다
It's March, middle of the semester.
(TRUCK BACKFIRES)
멋지군
Great.
- 차 좋은데
- 고마워
- Nice ride.
- Thanks.
잘했어
Good one.
너 새로온 이사벨라 스완이지
You're Isabella Swan, the new girl.
안녕, 난 이곳의 소식통 에릭이야
Hi, I'm Eric, the eyes and ears of this place.
필요한 거 있으면 말해
학교 안내, 점심 데이트, 기댈 어깨라든지
Anything you need, tour guide,
lunch date, shoulder to cry on?
난 조용히 삭히는 타입이라서
I'm really kind of the more
suffer-in-silence type.
좋은 헤드라인이네
Good headline for your feature.
내가 신문사에 있는데
넌 첫페이지 기사야
I'm on the paper,
and you're news, baby, front page.
아니, 안 돼
No, I'm not.
제발 그러지마
(STUTTERS) You...
Please don't have any sort of...
진정해, 기사 안 써
Chillax. No feature.
- 그래, 고마워
- 미안해
- Okay, thanks.
- Cool?
좋았어, 그렇게
GIRL: All right. Okay. Yeah.
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
잡아! 잡으라고
GIRL: Get it! Get it! Get it!
(BELLA GRUNTS)
너한테
GIRL 1 : To you!
이런
Whoa!
미안해
I'm sorry.
나 안 한다고 했는데
I told them not to let me play.
아냐, 잠깐 그게...
No way. No, no, no.
That's... That's... Don't...
너 이사벨라 맞지?
You're Isabella, right?
그냥 벨라
Just Bella.
그래 난 마이크
뉴튼이야
Yeah. Hey, I'm Mike Newton.
- 반가워
- 나도 그래
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, yeah.
- 얘 스파이크 잘 하지?
- 어, 그러네
- She's got a great spike, huh?
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah, it's...
난 제시카야
I'm Jessica, by the way.
너 아리조나에서 왔지?
Hey, you're from Arizona, right?
맞아
Yeah.
아리조나 사람들은
검게 타지 않나?
Aren't people from Arizona
supposed to be, like, really tan?
그렇지
Yeah.
그래서 날 쫒아냈나봐
Maybe that's why they kicked me out.
(MIKE AND JESSICA LAUGHING)
너 재밌다
You're good.
정말 웃겨
That's so funny.
- 제시카 빨리와
- 아래로
- Back in, Jess.
- BOY: Down here.
대단한 작품들처험
ERIC: Like a masterpiece, you know,
노아는 하늘에 뜬
피라미드 이야기를
we'll have, like,
this crazy pyramid fall from the sky,
- 할 수..
- 앉으시죠
- and then you guys can...
- It's my pleasure, Madame.
- 할 수 있을거야
- 브리토 먹을래?
- You guys can give each other high fives.
- Burrito, my friend?
- 마이크, 내 친구 벨라를 만났구나
- 그래?
- Hey, Mikey! You met my home girl, Bella?
- Hey.
네 친구라고?
Your home girl?
- 그래?
- 그럼
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- 그러니까
- 내 애인이지!
- That's...
- My girl.
네 게임을 망쳐서 미안!
Sorry I had to mess up your game, Mike!
타일러
Tyler.
(ALL LAUGHING)
그래!
TYLER: Yes!
세상에나
Oh, my God.
신입생이 된 거 같네
네가 새 장난감이야
It's like first grade all over again.
You're the shiny new toy.
웃어
Smile.
- 그래
- 미안
- Okay.
- Sorry.
기사에 필요해서
I needed a candid for the feature.
기사는 취소야, 앤젤라
The feature's dead, Angela.
얘기 꺼내지 마
Don't bring it up again.
괜찮아, 난 그냥
It's okay, I just...
내가 뒤를 봐줄게
I got your back, baby.
그럼 다시 청소년 음주
특집이나 써야겠다
Guess we'll just run another editorial
on teen drinking.
그런 것도 되잖아
섭식장애 라든가
You know,
you can always go for eating disorders.
수영팬티에 뽕 넣기
Speedo padding on the swim team.
그거 좋은데
Actually, that's a good one.
- 재밌지? 생각도 못 했는데
- 그래
- Kirk. Right? That's exactly what I thought.
- (LAUGHS) Yeah.
올림픽 사이즈 말이야
ANGELA: We're talking Olympic-size.
그렇게 말랐는데 말도 안 돼
JESSICA: There's no way. He's so skinny.
It doesn't make sense.
- 맞아, 파헤쳐봐
- 그래
- ANGELA: Totally.
- Yeah.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
쟤들은 누구야?
Who are they?
컬린 패거리
The Cullens.
저애들은 컬린 박사 부부의
수양자녀들이야
They're Dr. and Mrs. Cullen's foster kids.
몇년 전인가 알라스카에서
이사왔어
They moved down here from Alaska,
like, a few years ago.
자기들끼리만 어울려
They kind of keep to themselves.
모두 같이 지내거든
Yeah, 'cause they're all together.
정말 함께 지낸다고
Like, together, together.
금발이 로잘리이고
The blonde girl, that's Rosalie,
검은 머리가 에멧인데
둘이 사귀어
and the big dark-haired guy, Emmett,
they're, like, a thing.
그게 합법인지 모르겠어
I'm not even sure that's legal.
걔들이 실제 가족은 아니잖아
Jess, they're not actually related.
하지만 같이 사는데 이상하다구
Yeah, but they live together. It's weird.
그리고 검은 머리애가 앨리스야
And, okay, the little dark-haired girl's Alice.
쟤는 정말 별나
She's really weird,
금발 재스퍼하고 사귀는데
어디 아픈 애 같지
and she's with Jasper, the blond one
who looks like he's in pain.
컬린 박사는 양아버지면서 중매장이야
Dr. Cullen's like this foster dad/matchmaker.
나도 입양해줬으면
Maybe he'll adopt me.
쟤는 누구야?
Who's he?
에드워드 컬린이야
That's Edward Cullen.
보다시피 완전 짱이지
He's totally gorgeous, obviously,
여기엔 걸맞는 상대가 없나봐
but apparently nobody here's
good enough for him.
내가 신경쓰는 건 아니지만
Like I care, you know?
그런 거지
So, yeah.
정말이야
시간 낭비마
JESSICA: Seriously, like,
don't waste your time.
생각 없어
I wasn't planning on it.
- 몰리나 선생님
- 안녕, 마이크
- Mr. Molina.
- Hey, Mike.
그래, 스완양이군
Oh, yes. Miss Swan.
안녕, 통행증은? 고마워
Hi. Can I have the pass? Thank you.
환영하네, 여기 교재들
Welcome to the class.
Here. Here's your stuff, okay?
그리고 여기가 자리니까,
이리 오게
And I got a seat for you right here,
so come over.
마지막으로
진도를 잘 따라오게
The last one.
Just follow along till you catch up.
오늘은 플라나리아를
관찰하도록 한다
All right, guys, today we are gonna be
observing the behavior of planaria,
납작벌레라고도 하지
aka flatworms.
우리가 해야 할 것은
So what we're gonna do...
(MOLINA CONTINUES
TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
...재생한다
...regenerate.
좀비 벌레지
Zombie worms.
핸드폰은 금지야, 얘들아 시작하자
No cell phones. Guys, let's get to it.
조심하고 어떤 부분은
Gentle, gentle, certain areas.
이 부분은 자르지 마라
여기는 자르지 않을거야
Please just don't cut here.
We don't cut here.
이걸 믿지 않는구나
You won't believe this.
집중하자, 얘들아
사실을 확인하는 동안은
Let's try to focus
while we check those out, huh, guys?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
빈 곳이 있을 거예요
EDWARD: There must be something open.
- 물리, 생화학
- 강의가 다 찼어요
- Physics? Biochem?
- WOMAN: No, every class is full.
잠깐만요
Just a minute, dear.
그냥 생물을 들어야겠네요
I'm afraid you'll have to stay in biology.
좋아요
참아야겠군요
Fine. Just...
I'll just have to endure it.
몰라보게 자랐구나
그리고 예뻐졌고
I just can't get over how grown up you are.
And so gorgeous.
안녕 벨라
Hey, Bella.
나 기억하니?
You remember me?
산타 역할을 한 적이 있지
I played Santa one year.
웨일런, 얘는 4살 이후로
여기서 성탄절 안 지냈어
Yeah, Waylon, she hasn't had
a Christmas here since she was four.
그래도 강한 인상을 줬을 걸?
I bet I made an impression, though, didn't I?
- 항상 그러지
- 약 먹은 산타가요?
- You always do.
- Butt-crack Santa?
그래도 애들은 작은병 좋아했어
Hey, kids love those little bottles, though.
얘 밥 먹게둬요, 웨일런
All right,
let the girl eat her garden burger, Waylon.
다 먹고 좋아하는 거
가져다 줄게
As soon as you're done,
I will bring you your favorite.
딸기 파이, 기억나?
Berry cobbler, remember?
아빠는 아직도 드셔, 매주 목요일마다
Your dad still has it. Every Thursday.
고맙습니다, 저도 좋아해요
Thank you. That'd be great.
여깄다
CHARLIE: Here.
고마워요
(WHISPERS) Thanks.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
얘야, 들어봐
춘계 훈련일이 잘 되면
RENEE ON PHONE: Hey, baby. So, listen,
if spring training goes well,
우리 플로리다로 이사갈 거야
we could be moving to Florida.
추가 3분을 통화하시려면
1.25 달러를 넣어주세요
AUTOMATED VOICE: Please insert $1.25
for an additional three minutes.
엄마 휴대폰은?
Mom, where's your cell?
웃지마라
Okay, don't laugh.
충전기를 잃어버린 게 아냐, 도망갔어
I didn't lose my power cord. It ran away.
(LAUGHS)
비명을 지르면서
말 그대로 다 쫒아낸다니까
Screaming.
I literally repel technology now.
- 보고싶어요
- 아가, 나도 보고싶다
- I miss you.
- Oh, baby, I miss you, too.
학교 얘기 좀 해보렴
애들은 어떠니?
But tell me more about your school.
Now, what are the kids like?
귀여운 남자애 있어?
Are there any cute guys?
애들이 잘 대해주니?
Are they being nice to you?
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
그럼요
Well,
다들 환영해주죠
they're all very welcoming.
다 말해봐라
Tell me all about it.
별거 아닌걸요
It doesn't even matter.
얘야 그렇지 않아
Yes, it does, honey.
숙제해야돼요
나중에 통화해요
I have homework to do.
I'll talk to you later.
그래, 사랑한다
Okay. I love you.
저도요
Love you, too.
그애와 대면하기로 했다
문제가 뭔지 말해달랠거다
BELLA: I planned to confront him
and demand to know what his problem was.
그런데 안 나타났다
But he never showed.
(SLOW ROCK THEME PLAYING)
벨라!
Bella!
그리고 다음날도 안 나왔다
BELLA: And the next day, another no-show.
며칠이 지났다
More days passed.
돌아가는 게 좀 이상했다
Things were getting a little strange.
(PANTING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GRUNTS)
- 괜찮니?
- 네, 괜찮아요
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
얼음 때문에 중심잡기 힘드네요
Ice doesn't really help the uncoordinated.
맞아, 그래서 트럭에
새타이어를 달았지
Yeah. That's why I had
some new tires put on the truck.
낡은 건 많이 닳았거든
Old ones were getting pretty bald.
저녁에 늦을 거다
메이슨 마을에 가야돼
Well, probably be late for dinner.
I gotta head down to Mason County.
그리샴 제분소 경비가 동물에게
살해당했다는구나
Security guard at the Grisham Mill
got killed by some kind of animal.
동물이요?
An animal?
여긴 피닉스가 아니잖니 벨라
You're not in Phoenix anymore, Bells.
그래서 도와주려고
Anyway, I figured I'd lend a hand.
- 조심하세요
- 항상 조심하지
- Be careful.
- Always am.
- 타이어 감사해요
- 그래
- And thanks for the tires.
- Yeah.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
무도회 위원도 좋지만
ERIC: Prom Committee is a chick thing,
난 기사취재를 해야되고
but I gotta cover it for the paper anyway,
음악선택을 도와줄 사람이 있었으면 해
and they need a guy
to help choose the music,
그래서 네 선곡 목록이 필요해
so I need your play list.
있지, 궁금한 게 있는데
너 혹시 같이 갈...
Hey, listen, I was wondering,
did you have a date to...
잘 지내, 아리조나?
What's up, Arizona? Huh?
비오는 거 좋아해?
How you liking the rain, girl?
익숙해지는 게 좋을거야
Better get used to it, girl.
그래, 마이크 너 참 귀엽다
Yeah, Mike, hey, you're real cute, man.
- 그래 나도 알아
- 정말로 대단했어
- Oh, I know...
- That was really awesome.
네가 내 게임을 망치고 있어
게임 한판 하자
ERIC: Why you shooting down my game?
Let a playa play.
그래 좋아
뭐하고 놀건데, T-Ball?
MIKE: Yeah, okay.
What you playing at, T-Ball?
안녕
Hello.
지난 주에 인사할 기회가
없었는데 미안하다
I'm sorry, I didn't get a chance
to introduce myself last week.
난 에드워드 컬린이야
I'm Edward Cullen.
넌 벨라지?
You're Bella?
그래
Yes.
양파의 뿌리 세포
Onion root tip cells,
그게 슬라이드에 들어 있다
that's what's on your slides right now.
세포 분열 단계를
표시하고 분류해라, 알겠니?
Okay? So, separate and label them
into the phases of mitosis,
제일 먼저 하는 조에게는
황금 양파를 상으로 준다
and the first partners that get it right
are gonna win the Golden Onion.
(STUDENTS CATCALLING)
좋았어
BOY: All right, good.
숙녀 먼저
Ladies first.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
안 나왔었잖아
You were gone.
그래
Yeah.
한 며칠 시외에 나가 있었어
I was out of town for a couple of days.
개인 사정으로
Personal reasons.
전기(前期) 과정이야
Prophase.
내가 봐도 될까?
Do you mind if I look?
전기(前期)네
It's prophase.
내가 그랬잖아
Like I said.
비오는 거 좋아해?
So are you enjoying the rain?
(ANXIOUS LAUGH)
뭐?
What?
날씨에 대해 묻는 거야?
You're asking me about the weather?
그래
Yeah, I...
그러는 거지
I guess I am.
비를 좋아하지는 않아
Well, I don't really like the rain.
뭐든지 차갑고 축축한 것은 별로야
Any cold, wet thing, I don't really...
- 왜?
- 아니야
- What?
- Nothing.
(LAUGHS)
후기(後期)야
It's anaphase.
- 확인해봐도 돼?
- 물론
- You mind if I check?
- Sure.
후기(後期) 맞네
Anaphase.
내가 그랬잖아
Like I said.
추위와 비가 싫으면
If you hate the cold and the rain so much,
왜 미국에서 가장
습한 곳으로 왔어?
why'd you move to the wettest place
in the continental US?
좀 복잡해
It's complicated.
알아들을 수 있어
I'm sure I can keep up.
엄마가 결혼을 하셔서
My mom remarried, and...
그 남자가 싫은 거야? 아니면
So you don't like the guy, or...
아니, 그건 아니고
No, that's not...
필은 좋은 분이야
Phil's really nice.
(GENTLE THEME PLAYING)
중기(中期)야
확인해볼래?
It's metaphase.
You want to check it?
널 믿을게
I believe you.
엄마랑 필과 함께
이사올 수도 있었잖아?
Why didn't you move
with your mother and Phil?
필은 마이너리그 야구선수야
Well, Phil's a minor league baseball player,
여행을 많이 다녀
and he travels a lot,
엄마는 나와 함께 집에 있었지만
우울해 하는 걸 알았지
and my mom stayed home with me,
but I knew it made her unhappy,
그래서 내가 한동안 아빠와 있기로 한 거야
so I figured I'd stay with my dad for a while.
그래서 지금은 네가 우울하구나
And now you're unhappy.
- 아니야
- 미안해, 난 단지
- No.
- I'm sorry, I'm just...
그냥 너를 알아보려는 거야
I'm just trying to figure you out.
널 읽기가 아주 어려워
You're very difficult for me to read.
너 렌즈 꼈니?
Hey, did you get contacts?
아니
No.
눈이 검은색이었어
전에 봤을 때는
Your eyes were black
the last time I saw you,
지금은 금갈색으로 보이네
and now they're, like, golden brown.
알아, 그게...
Yeah, I know, it's the...
형광등 때문에 그래
It's the fluorescents.
(HORN BLASTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LOUD THUDS)
(LOUD GRUNT)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
- 벨라!
- ALL: Bella!
- Bella!
(STUDENTS CLAMORING)
911에 연락해!
GIRL: Dial 911
이미 전화했어
조만간 누군가 올거야
BOY: I already called.
They're gonna send somebody over soon.
벨라, 정말 미안해, 너무 당황해서
Bella, I'm so sorry. I panicked.
벨라, 911 전화했어
Bella, I've got 911 on the phone now.
벨라, 너 괜찮아?
Bella. You okay?
넌 이따가 얘기 좀 하자
괜찮은 거야?
You and I are gonna talk.
You all right?
괜찮아요, 진정하세요
I'm fine, Dad. Calm down.
미안해 벨라, 서려고 했어
I'm sorry, Bella. I tried to stop.
알아, 괜찮아
I know. It's okay.
아니, 괜찮은 게 아니야
No. It sure as hell is not okay.
저 친구 잘못 아니예요
Dad, it wasn't his fault.
넌 죽을 뻔 했어
그건 알겠니?
You could've been killed.
You understand that?
하지만 안 죽었어요
Yes. But I wasn't, so...
넌 면허취소인줄 알아
You can kiss your license goodbye.
- 서장님 따님이 왔다구요?
- 아, 컬린 박사님
- I heard the chief's daughter was here.
- CHARLIE: Dr. Cullen.
찰리
Charlie.
제가 맡을게요, 재키
I've got this one, Jackie.
이사벨라
Isabella.
벨라예요
Bella.
벨라, 큰일을 당했군요
기분은 어때요?
Well, Bella, looks like you took quite a spill.
How do you feel?
좋아요
Good.
여길 봐요
Look here.
외상후 스트레스나
감각상실이 올 수 있지만
You might experience some
post-traumatic stress or disorientation,
신체 징후도 좋고
but your vitals look good.
머리 부상도 없네요
No signs of any head trauma.
괜찮을 것 같네요
I think you'll be just fine.
정말 미안해, 벨라
TYLER: I'm so sorry, Bella. I'm really...
아시겠지만
정말 큰일날 뻔 했어요
You know,
it would've been a whole lot worse
만약 에드워드가 없었다면요
그애가 저를 밀어냈어요
if Edward wasn't there.
He knocked me out of the way.
에드워드? 선생님 아들이요?
Edward? Your boy?
네, 대단했어요
Yeah, it was amazing.
그앤 멀리 서있었는데
굉장히 빨리 왔어요
I mean, he got to me so fast.
He was nowhere near me.
아주 다행이었군요
Sounds like you were very lucky.
찰리
Charlie.
나는 서류 작성을
해야하니 너는...
I gotta go sign some paperwork.
You should...
엄마한테 전화해라
You should probably call your mom.
말씀하셨어요?
Did you tell her?
엄마는 아마...
(GROANS) She's probably just
난리나셨겠네요
freaking out.
애들 15명이 그 일을 봤어
ROSALIE: fifteen kids that saw
what happened.
그럼 어떻게 해요?
죽게 내버려 둬요?
EDWARD: What was I supposed to do, then?
Let her die?
이건 너만의 일이 아냐
우리 모두의 일이지
This isn't just about you.
It's about all of us.
사무실로 가는 게 좋겠다
CARLISLE: I think we should
take this in my office.
- 얘기 좀 할 수 있어?
- 로잘리
- Can I talk to you for a minute?
- Rosalie.
뭐?
What?
어떻게 그렇게 빨리 왔어?
How did you get over to me so fast?
네 옆에 서 있었어, 벨라
I was standing right next to you, Bella.
아니야, 넌 주차장 건너편
차 옆에 서 있었어
No. You were next to your car,
across the lot.
안 그랬어
No, I wasn't.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
그랬다니까
Yes, you were.
벨라, 넌 머리를 부딪혔어
Bella, you're... You hit your head.
그래서 혼동하는거야
I think you're confused.
내가 본 건 알아
I know what I saw.
그게 정확히 뭔데?
And what exactly was that?
네가
You...
벤을 막아냈어
You stopped the van.
손으로 밀어냈잖아
You pushed it away with your hand.
아무도 안 믿을 거야
Well, nobody's gonna believe you, so...
얘기하지 않을 거야
I wasn't gonna tell anybody.
그냥 사실을 알고 싶어
I just need to know the truth.
그냥 고맙다고 하고 잊으면 안 돼?
Can't you just thank me and get over it?
고마워
Thank you.
- 눈감아주지 않을 거지?
- 안 해
- You're not gonna let this go, are you?
- No.
그럼 실망해도 뭐라지 마
Well, then I hope you enjoy disappointment.
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
그 때가 에드워드 꿈을 꾼
첫날밤이었다
BELLA: And that was the first night
I dreamt of Edward Cullen.
모두들 허가증을 줘
I need everybody's permission slips, okay?
- 새미가 모아라
- 네
- Sammy, please collect them.
- Yeah.
얘들아 출발하자
Guys, let's go.
서둘러 타고 출발하자
Come on, get in. ln. Let's go!
어디 보자, 살아있구나!
Look at you, huh? You're alive.
- 그래, 갈 때가 안된 거지
- 그러네
- I know, yeah. False alarm, I guess.
- Yeah.
물어보고 싶었는데
너도 알겠지만
Now, I wanted to ask you,
you know, if, you know,
한 달이나 남긴 했지만
it's like a month away, but...
(MIKE LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
나와 무도회 갈래?
Do you wanna go to prom with me?
그래, 어떻게 생각해?
So, what do you think?
- 뭐를?
- 가고 싶어?
- About what?
- Do you want to go?
무도회 말야
To prom?
나하고?
With me?
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
난...
I...
무도회라...
Prom.
춤추게?
Dancing.
좋은 생각은 아닌데
Not such a good idea for me.
그 주말에 할 일이 있어
I have something that weekend anyway.
그 때 잭슨빌에 가야해
I'm going to Jacksonville that weekend.
다른 주말에 가면 안 돼?
You can't go another weekend?
환불이 안되는 표라서
Non-refundable ticket.
제시카한테 가자고 해
You should ask Jessica.
너랑 가고 싶어 하거든
I know she wants to go with you.
알았어
All right. All right.
이봐, 얘들아! 빨리 와라
MOLINA: Yo, yo, yo. Hey, guys, come on.
이제 가야한다, 가야해
녹색이 뭐지? 좋은 거지
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Green is what? Good.
얘들아, 어서 가자
Let's go. Guys, come on.
다른 버스로 가라! 가자!
Other bus, other bus. Let's go.
계란 껍질, 당근 잎사귀
MOLINA: Egg shells, carrot tops.
혼합물은 정말 멋지지
그 안에 모두 들어있어, 에릭
Compost is cool.
Now, stuff that in there, Eric.
- 예, 선생님
- 좋아, 아주 좋아
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
- Very good, very good.
내가 뜨끈뜨끈한
혼합물 차를 만들지
Now, I am gonna make a steaming cup
of compost tea.
- 좋아요
- 이리 주세요
- Okay.
- Give me that.
이게 재활용의
기본적인 형태지
Yeah. This is recycling
in its most basic form, guys.
마시지마! 나무 줄 거야
Don't drink it! It's for the plants.
잭슨빌에 뭐가 있지?
What's in Jacksonville?
그걸 어떻게 알았어?
How did you know about that?
내 질문에 대답 안 했잖아
You didn't answer my question.
너도 내 질문에 대답 안 했으니
You don't answer any of mine, so...
인사도 안 했잖아
I mean, you don't even say hi to me.
안녕
Hi.
차를 어떻게 막았는지
말해줄 거야?
Are you gonna tell me
how you stopped the van?
그래, 아드레날린 급증이 일어났어
Yeah. I had an adrenaline rush.
흔한 일이니까 인터넷 검색해봐
It's very common. You can Google it.
플로리다 사람들
Floridians.
그게 잭슨빌에 있어
That's what's in Jacksonville.
좀 보면서 걸어
Can you at least watch where you walk?
늘 까칠하게 굴어서 미안한데
그게 최선이라 그래
Look, I'm sorry I'm being rude all the time.
I just think it's the best way.
벨라! 누가 무도회 가자고 했게?
Bella! Guess who just asked me to prom.
누가?
Who?
마이크가 너한테
물어볼 줄 알았는데
Yeah, I actually totally thought
that Mike was gonna ask you.
- 어색한 거 아니지?
- 아니, 전혀
- It's not gonna be weird, though, right?
- No. Zero weirdness.
- 너희 잘 어울려
- 나도 알아
- You guys are great together.
- I know, right?
(GUYS HOOTING)
- 타일러
- 역겹다
- Tyler...
- BOY: Gross.
벨라 이것봐, 지렁이야
Bella, look. It's a worm.
지렁이
(GUFFAWING) It's a worm.
벨라 우린 친구하면 안 돼
Bella, we shouldn't be friends.
더 일찍 결정했어야지
You really should've figured
that out a little earlier.
그냥 깔려죽게
놔두지 그랬어?
I mean, why didn't you just
let the van crush me
이렇게 후회할 거라면
and save yourself all this regret?
구해준 걸 후회하는 거 같아?
What, you think I regret saving you?
그러는 게 보여
이유는 모르겠지만
I can see that you do.
I just... I don't know why.
넌 아무것도 몰라
You don't know anything.
안녕
Hi.
우리랑 같이 탈 거니?
Are you gonna be riding with us?
아니, 버스 다 찼어
No, our bus is full.
엄마가 또 전화했다
Your mom called. Again.
음, 그건 아빠탓이예요
Well, that's your fault.
사고날 뻔한 거 말하지 마셨어야죠
다 드셨어요?
You shouldn't have told her
about the ''almost'' accident. You finished?
그래
Yeah.
네 말이 맞아
네 엄마는 항상 걱정하는 법을 알고 있었지
Yeah, I suppose you're right.
She always did know how to worry.
엄마 달라졌던데
She seems different.
행복해 보이고
She seems happy.
필도 괜찮은 사람 같던데
Phil sounds like an all right guy.
좋아요
Yeah, he is.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHS)
좋다고?
All right.
아니야, 넌 장갑이 필요해
정말로 필요해
ERIC: No, you need the mitts.
You need them.
아니, 왜 계속 나와 논쟁하는거야?
너 장갑을 껴야 한다고
No, why do you keep arguing with me?
You just need them.
- 넌 동상걸릴거야
- 나도 모르겠다
- ERIC: You're gonna get frostbite!
- I don't even know.
이봐
ERIC: Yeah. Hey!
- 라 푸시 베이비, 갈래?
- 무슨 뜻이야?
- La Push, baby. You in?
- Should I know what that means?
퀼루트 인디언구역의 라 푸시 해변
우리 모두 내일 갈거야
La Push Beach down at the Quileute Rez.
We're all going tomorrow.
- 그래, 파도가 몰려온데
- 난 인터넷만 서핑하는 게 아냐
- Yeah, there's a big swell coming in.
- And I don't just surf the Internet.
에릭, 한 번 일어섰잖아
스티로폼 탄 거고
Eric, you stood up once,
and it was a foam board.
고래 구경도 있어
같이 가자
But there's whale watching, too.
Come with us.
라 푸시 베이비, 라 푸시
La Push, baby. It's La Push.
그 소리 그만하면 갈게
Okay, I'll go if you stop saying that, okay?
정말이야, 징그러
Seriously, dude. It's creepy, man.
- 뭘? 원래 그렇게 부른다구
- 그래서
- What? That's what it's called.
- So...
음식 예술인가?
EDWARD: Edible art?
벨라
Bella.
고마워
Thanks.
너의 변덕스런 기분에
적응이 안 돼
You know, your mood swings
are kind of giving me whiplash.
친구하면 안 된다는 말이지
I only said it'd be better
if we weren't friends,
원치 않는다는 건 아냐
not that I didn't wanna be.
그게 무슨 소리야?
What does that mean?
네가 똑똑하다면
나를 멀리할 거야
It means if you were smart,
you'd stay away from me.
논쟁하자는 거면 내가
안 똑똑하다고 하고
Okay, well, let's say for argument's sake
that I'm not smart.
- 사실을 말해줄 거야?
- 아니, 그렇지 않아
- Would you tell me the truth?
- No, probably not.
네 추측을 듣고 싶어
I'd rather hear your theories.
생각해봤는데
I have considered
방사능 거미와 크립토나이트가 떠올랐어
radioactive spiders and Kryptonite.
모두 슈퍼영웅들이잖아?
That's all superhero stuff, right?
만약에 내가 영웅이 아니고
혹시 악당이라면?
What if I'm not the hero?
What if I'm the bad guy?
넌 아니잖아
You're not.
왜 연기를 하는지 모르겠지만
I can see what you're trying to put off,
그러면 사람들을 멀어지게
할 뿐이야
but I can see that it's just
to keep people away from you.
그건 가면이야
It's a mask.
우리 그냥 어울리면 어때?
Why don't we just hang out?
모두들 해변에 갈 거야
Everybody's going to the beach.
같이 가
Come.
내 말은 그냥 즐기자고
I mean, have fun.
- 어디 해변?
- 라 푸시
- Which beach?
- La Push.
글쎄, 모르겠네
I don't know.
난...
I just...
그 해변에 문제 있어?
Is there something wrong with that beach?
애들이 많아서
It's just a little crowded.
(SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
- 엄청 추운데
- 타고 나간다
- Hey, it's freezing.
- I'm paddling out, Coates.
- 이럴 가치가 있나
- 여기까지 왔잖아
- I don't know if it's worth it anymore.
- We drove all the way out here.
- 타고 나가야지
- 그래
- JESSICA: I'm at least paddling out.
- Yeah.
- 제시카 말이 맞아
- 너희들은 겁장이야
- She's right.
- You guys are babies.
에릭의 무도회 신청을
기다리고 있어
So, I keep thinking that Eric's
gonna ask me to the prom,
그런데 안 하네
and then he just doesn't.
네가 신청해
You should ask him.
주도권을 잡아
넌 강하고 독립적인 여성이야
Take control.
You're a strong, independent woman.
- 내가?
- 그럼
- I am?
- Yes.
- 지퍼 올려줄래?
- 그래?
- Hey, will you do me up?
- Yeah.
- 벨라!
- 안녕, 제이콥
- Bella!
- Hi, Jacob.
- 얘들아, 제이콥이야
- 안녕, 반갑다
- Guys, this is Jacob.
- Hey, guys. How you doing?
- 안녕
- Hi.
나 스토킹하는 거야?
What are you, like, stalking me?
내 구역에 들어왔잖아
(SCOFFS) You're on my rez, remember?
서핑해?
Are you surfing?
- 절대 못 하지
- 고마워
- Definitely not.
- Thanks.
너희들이 벨라 친구해줘
데이트 상대가 안 왔어
You guys should keep Bella company.
Her date bailed.
데이트라니?
What date?
에드워드를 불렀어
She invited Edward.
- 예의상 그랬어
- 초대한 거 잘한 거야
- To be polite, that's it.
- I think it's nice she invited him.
- 아무도 안 하잖아
- 컬린애들 괴물이잖아
- Nobody ever does.
- Yeah, 'cause Cullen's a freak.
맞는 말이야
You got that right.
너희들도 알아?
You guys know him?
컬린 애들은 여기 안 와
The Cullens don't come here.
친구들 무슨 소리야?
컬린이 여기 안 온다니?
What did your friends mean about,
you know, ''The Cullens don't come here?''
눈치챘구나
You caught that, huh?
말하면 안 되는 건데
I'm not really supposed
to say anything about it.
비밀 지킬 수 있어
Hey, I can keep a secret.
(LAUGHS)
그냥 오래된 무서운 이야기야
Really, it's just like an old scary story.
알고 싶어
Well, I want to know.
퀼루트 인디언이 늑대의
후손이란 건 아니?
Okay, did you know Quileutes
are supposedly descended from wolves?
뭐? 늑대?
What? Like, wolves?
- 그래
- 진짜 늑대 말이야?
- Yeah.
- Like, real wolves?
우리 부족의 전설이지
JACOB: Well, that's the legend of our tribe.
좋아
BELLA: Okay.
그래 컬린에 대한 이야기는?
So what's the story about the Cullens?
그게 그들은 원수 일파의
후손이라는 거지
Well, they're supposedly descended
from this, like, enemy clan.
증조부 추장님이 우리 땅에서
사냥하는 걸 발견하셨어
JACOB: My great grandfather, the chief,
found them hunting on our land.
하지만 그들은 다른 부류라고 주장했데
But they claimed to be something different,
그래서 우리는 그들과 협정을 맺었지
so we made a treaty with them.
그들이 퀼루트 땅에 들어오지 않는다면
If they promised to stay off Quileute lands,
창백한 얼굴의 그들 정체를
밝히지 않기로 했어
then we wouldn't expose
what they really were to the palefaces.
컬린 일가는 최근에 이사온 줄 알았는데
I thought they just moved here.
아니면 다시 돌아온 걸지도 몰라
Or just moved back.
그렇군
Right.
내 손을 건드렸어
뱀이야, 멈춰
ANGELA: (SCREAMS) It touched my hand.
A snake! Stop!
그들의 진짜 정체가 뭐야?
Well, what are they really?
그냥 이야기야, 벨라
It's just a story, Bella.
자, 이만 가자
Come on, let's go.
(ANGELA CONTINUES SCREAMING)
뱀이다! 뱀
A snake! A snake!
엄마는 내가 고양이를
울게 할 수 없다고 하셨지
(SINGING) My mama said I didn't know
how to make a kitty meow
(DEEP GROWL)
누구세요?
Hello?
제럴드?
Gerald?
(WHOOSHING)
안녕하세요
Hello.
자켓 좋은데
Nice jacket.
누구신지?
Who are you?
늘 똑같은 질문이군
It's always the same inane questions.
넌 누구냐?
''Who are you?''
뭘 원하냐?
''What do you want?''
왜 이러는 거냐?
''Why are you doing this?''
제임스, 음식가지고 장난치지 말자
James, let's not play with our food.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(SLOW BLUESY-ROCK THEME PLAYING)
퀼루트 전설
썬더버드 서점
약도 - 포트 엔젤리스
그애는 없어
JESSICA: He's not here.
날씨가 화창할 때마다
컬린 애들은 사라져
Whenever the weather's nice,
the Cullens disappear.
그냥들 사라진다고?
What, do they just ditch?
아니, 컬린 박사 부부가
캠핑같은 거 간다나봐
No, Dr. and Mrs. Cullen yank them out
for, like, hiking and camping and stuff.
우리 부모님도
그랬으면 좋은데
I tried that out on my parents.
Not even close.
나 에릭하고 무도회 가
Guys, I'm going to the prom with Eric.
- 내가 신청하고 주도권을 잡았지
- 그럴 거라고 했지
- I just asked him. I took control.
- I told you that would happen.
너 정말 지방에 가야돼?
Are you sure you have to go out of town?
그래 가족 일이라
Oh, yeah, it's a little family thing.
우리도 포트 앤젤러스로 쇼핑가야지
Okay, we should go shopping
in Port Angeles
예쁜 드레스가 바닥나지 전에 말이야
before all the good dresses get cleaned out.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
포트 엔젤리스라고? 나도 가도돼?
Port Angeles? You mind if I come?
그래, 네 의견 들어야지
Yeah, I need your opinion.
- 이게 맘에 든다
- 정말 멋지다
- I like this one.
- ANGELA: That's cool.
어깨 한쪽은 글쎄
But, like, I don't know about
the one-shoulder thing.
- 이거 좋다
- 그래, 구슬장식이 예쁘네
- I like this one.
- JESSICA: Yeah, I like the beading,
- 그거라면 목걸이 할 필요도 없겠다
- 제시카, 라벤더 어때?
- and you wouldn't need jewelry.
- Jess, what do you think? Lavender?
- 좋아? 색깔 어울려?
- 맘에 든다
- Is that good? Is that my color?
- I like it.
장미색도 좋아
I liked that dusty rose one, too.
난 이게 맘에 들어
가슴이 예뻐 보이잖아
Okay, I like this one.
It makes my boobs look good.
- 이봐
- 그렇지?
- Hey.
- JESSICA: Right?
훌륭한데
Nice.
- 이런
- 이거 민망하네
- ANGELA: Oh, God.
- That is uncomfortable.
역겹다
That's disgusting.
벨라, 어떤 거 같아?
Bella, what do you think?
응?
Yes?
멋져보인다
That looks great.
아까 입은 것도
맘에 든다며
You said that about, like,
the last five dresses, though.
전부 다 예뻐
I thought they were all pretty good.
이런 데 관심없구나?
You're not really into this, are you?
사실은 서점에
가고 싶었어
I actually really just want
to go to this bookstore.
식당에서 만날래?
I'll meet you guys at the restaurant?
- 정말로?
- 그래, 이따 보자
- JESSICA: Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah. I'll see you in a minute.
- 알았어.
- 좋아
- Okay.
쟤 말이 맞아, 정말 끝내준다
She's right, though. This looks awesome.
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
여깄습니다
MAN: There you go.
- 안녕히 가세요
- 고맙습니다
- Have a good night.
- BELLA: Thank you.
- 옷가게에서 널 봤어
- 이봐, 어딜 도망가?
- BOY: Saw you in the dress store.
- Hey, where you running to?
저기 있다
BOY: There she is.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 이쁜 아가씨네?
- What's up?
- It's my girl.
- 너희들 어떻게 지내?
- 우리가 누굴 찾았는데 봐
- BOY 2: How you guys doing?
- Look who we just found.
아가씨, 무슨 일이야?
어딜 가는데?
What's up, girl? Hey, Where you going?
- 어딜 가?
- 우리랑 술 한잔 하자
- BOY 3: Where are you going?
- Come get a drink with us.
- 그래, 우리랑 놀자구
- 이리 와
- Yeah, you should hang out with us.
- Come on.
재밌다구
It's fun.
- 문제 있나?
- 놀고 싶지 않은가봐
- What's the problem?
- She doesn't like that, man.
- 예쁘네
- 손대지 말아요
- You're pretty.
- Don't touch me.
- 귀엽다
- 싫다고 해도 해야 할걸
- BOY: Cute.
- Really, no. Seriously, you should.
손대지 말아요
Don't touch me.
(BOY GROANS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(GASPS)
차에 타!
Get in the car.
그거 아주 위험한 짓...
That was a very dangerous maneuver.
(DEEP GROWL)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BOYS SHOUTING)
(HORN BLARING)
돌아가서 머리통을
뽑아버려야 할까봐
I should go back there
and rip those guys' heads off.
그러면 안 돼
No, you shouldn't.
너는 놈들의 더럽고
혐오스런 생각을 몰라
You don't know the vile, repulsive things
they were thinking.
넌 알아?
And you do?
짐작할 수 있잖아
It's not hard to guess.
다른 얘기 좀 해줄래?
돌아갈 생각 안 나도록
Can you talk about something else?
Distract me so I won't turn around.
너 안전벨트 매야지
You should put your seatbelt on.
(LAUGHS)
너 안전벨트 매라
You should put your seatbelt on.
- 샐러드 정말 맛있었어
- 얘들아, 미안해
- I thought the salad was pretty good.
- Hey, you guys, I'm sorry. I just...
어딨었어? 메세지 남겼는데
Where were you? We left you messages.
기다리다가
배가 고파서
Yeah, we waited, but we were, like,
starving, so we...
벨라 못 가게해서 미안
I'm sorry I kept Bella from dinner.
둘이 마주쳤는데
얘기하느라고
We just sort of ran into each other
and got talking.
- 그래
- 괜찮아
- Yeah.
- No.
아니, 우린 완전 이해해
그럴 수도 있잖아?
No, we totally understand.
I mean, that happens, right?
그래, 우린
Yeah, we were...
- 우린 가는 중이었어
- 차타자
- We were, yeah, we were just leaving. So...
- Let's get this...
벨라 네가 원한다면...
Bella, if you wanna...
벨라가 뭐 좀 먹게
해줘야겠어
I think I should make sure
Bella gets something to eat.
네가 원하면
If you'd like.
직접 집에 태워다줄게
I'll drive you home myself.
그거 사려깊다
That's so thoughtful.
아주 자상한데
It's really thoughtful. Yeah.
그래, 뭐 좀 먹어야지
Yeah. I should eat something.
그래
Yeah.
- 그럼 내일 보자
- 좋아
- Okay, so we'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay, yeah.
- 내일 보자
- 그래
- ANGELA: See ya.
- Okay.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
버섯 라비올리 하나요
All right, one mushroom ravioli.
- 고마워요
- 맛있게 드세요
- Thanks.
- Yeah, no problem.
손님은 드시고 싶은 게
없으신가요?
So are you sure there isn't anything
I can get for you?
아뇨. 됐어요
No. No, thank you.
있으면 알려주세요
Let me know.
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
정말 안 먹어?
You're really not gonna eat?
됐어, 특별 다이어트 중이야
No, I'm on a special diet.
나한테 설명을 해줘야지
You gotta give me some answers.
그래, 아니
Yes, no.
다른 쪽에 접하려면
To get to the other side.
1.77245...
파이의 제곱근은 필요없어
I don't want to know
what the square root of pi is.
알고 있어?
You knew that?
나 어딨는지 어떻게 알았어?
How did you know where I was?
몰랐어
I didn't.
- 알았어
- 뭐?
- All right.
- What?
가지마, 벨라
Don't leave. I...
나 쫒아온 거야?
Did you follow me?
난...
I...
난 널 많이 보호하게 돼
I feel very protective of you.
그래서 쫒아왔구나
So you followed me.
네가 도움이 필요없으면
거리를 유지하려했는데
I was trying to keep a distance
unless you needed my help,
그 놈들의 생각을 듣게 됐어
and then I heard what those low-lifes
were thinking.
잠깐
Wait.
그들의 생각을 들었다고?
You say you heard what they were thinking?
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
그래서 너는
So what, you...
마음을 읽는구나
You read minds?
이 방안의 모든 생각을 읽을 수 있어
I can read every mind in this room.
너는 빼고
Apart from yours.
돈, 섹스
There's money, sex,
돈
money,
섹스
sex,
고양이
cat.
(SIGHS)
그리고 너는 알 수 없어
And then you, nothing.
그래서 갑갑해
It's very frustrating.
내가 잘못된 거야?
Is there something wrong with me?
마음을 읽는 건 나라고 말했는데
See, I tell you I can read minds,
너는 네가 잘못됐다고 생각하네
and you think there's
something wrong with you.
(EXHALES)
왜 그래?
What is it?
난 더이상 너와
떨어져 있을 자신이 없어
I don't have the strength
to stay away from you anymore.
그럼 그러지마
Then don't.
이젠 따뜻한 거 같아
Okay, I think I'm warm enough now.
(GASPS)
손이 아주 차네
Your hand is so cold.
어...
BELLA: Whoa!
무슨 일이지?
What is going on?
아빠가 아직 계시네
My dad's still here.
세워줄래?
Can you pull in?
끝에 우리 아빠 차야
EDWARD: That's my father's car on the end.
여기서 뭐 하시지?
What is he doing here?
아빠, 무슨 일이에요?
EDWARD: Carlisle, what's going on?
웨일런씨가 집 근처
배에서 발견됐다
Waylon Forge was found in a boat
out near his place.
- 시체를 검사했지
- 돌아가셨어요?
- I just examined the body.
- He died?
- 어떻게요?
- 짐승의 공격으로
- How?
- Animal attack.
메이슨의 경비원도
똑같지 않나요?
Was it the same one that
got that security guard down in Mason?
그럴 거예요
Most likely.
- 시내와 가까워지네요
- 벨라, 안으로 들어가요
- Well, it's getting closer to town, then.
- Bella, you should go inside.
웨일런씨는 아버지 친구분이었잖아요
Waylon was your father's friend.
알았어요
Okay.
나중에 봐
I'll see you later.
(MAN CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
- 아빠
- 왔니
- Hey.
안 되셨어요
Dad, I'm really sorry.
30년 지기였는데
I've known him going on 30 years.
걱정마라, 우리가 찾아낼 거다
Don't worry, we're gonna find this thing.
그동안
Meantime,
이걸 가지고 다녀라
I want you to carry this with you.
- 그거 별로
- 아빠가 안심이 될 거야
- I don't know if you...
- It'll give your old man some peace of mind.
알았어요
Okay.
집에 가자
Let's go home.
냉혈인
Cold One.
애포탐킨
(인디안 전설의 악마)
이집트 - 영생의 물
인도
페루
불사(不死)불사
속도
힘
(ECHOING BOOM)
차가운 피부
영생
흡혈
(BREATH TREMBLING)
넌 불가능할 정도로 빠르고 힘세
You're impossibly fast and strong.
피부는 창백하고 얼음처럼 차가워
Your skin is pale white and ice-cold.
눈의 색이 변하고
Your eyes change color.
어떤 때는 말하는 게
다른 시대에서 온 것 같아
And sometimes you speak
like you're from a different time.
먹지도 마시지도 않고
햇빛에 나가지도 않아
You never eat or drink anything.
You don't go out in the sunlight.
(BELLA GASPS QUIETLY)
몇 살이야?
How old are you?
열 일곱
Seventeen.
열 일곱으로 얼마나 살았어?
How long have you been 17?
좀 됐어
A while.
네 정체를 알아
I know what you are.
말해
Say it.
크게
Out loud.
말해
Say it.
뱀파이어
Vampire.
두려워?
Are you afraid?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
아니
No.
그럼 기본적인 걸 물어봐
Then ask me the most basic question.
뭘 먹는지
What do we eat?
날 해치지 않을 거야
You won't hurt me.
어디 가는 거야?
Where are we going?
산위로
Up the mountain.
구름이 걷힌 곳
Out of the cloud bank.
햇빛 속에서 내 모습을 봐야 돼
You need to see what
I look like in the sunlight.
(BELLA PANTING)
햇빛 속에서 우리를
보이지 않는 이유야
This is why we don't show
ourselves in sunlight.
사람들이 다른 걸 알게되거든
People would know we're different.
이게 나야
This is what I am.
(GASPING)
다이아몬드 같아
It's like diamonds.
아름다워
You're beautiful.
아름다워?
Beautiful?
이건 살인자의 피부야
This is the skin of a killer, Bella.
난 살인자야
I'm a killer.
난 안 믿어
I don't believe that.
넌 거짓을 믿으니까
That's because you believe the lie.
변장 말이야
It's camouflage.
난 세상에서 가장 위험한 사냥꾼이야
I'm the world's most dangerous predator.
나의 모든 것이 너를 끌어당겨
Everything about me invites you in,
나의 목소리, 나의 얼굴, 나의 체취까지
my voice, my face, even my smell.
그런 걸 이용할 필요도 없지
As if I would need any of that.
(LOUD WHOOSH)
네가 나를 이길 수 있을 것 같아?
As if you could outrun me!
(WHOOSHING)
나를 물리칠 수 있을 것 같아?
As if you could fight me off.
난 죽이도록 만들어졌어
I'm designed to kill.
상관 안 해
I don't care.
전에 사람도 죽여봤어
I've killed people before.
상관없어
It does not matter.
널 죽이고 싶어
I wanted to kill you.
이렇게 인간의 피를
원한 적이 평생 없었어
I've never wanted a human's blood
so much in my life.
너를 믿어
I trust you.
믿지마
Don't.
여기 왔잖아, 너를 믿어
I'm here. I trust you.
(WHOOSH)
우리 가족은 그 중에서도 달라
My family,
we're different from others of our kind.
우린 동물만 사냥해
We only hunt animals.
욕구를 통제하는 법을 배웠지
We've learned to control our thirst.
하지만 너, 너의 체취
But it's you, your scent,
나에겐 마약 같아
it's like a drug to me.
나만을 위한 개인 헤로인이지
You're like
my own personal brand of heroin.
(WHOOSH)
처음에 왜 그렇게 날 싫어했어?
Why did you hate me
so much when we met?
그랬지
I did.
널 너무 원하지 않게하려고
Only for making me want you so badly.
자제할 수 있을지 아직 모르겠어
I still don't know if I can control myself.
할 수 있는 거 알아
I know you can.
너의 마음을 읽을 수 없어
I can't read your mind.
네 생각을 말해줘야해
You have to tell me what you're thinking.
지금은 두려워
Now I'm afraid.
좋아
Good.
네가 두렵지는 않아
I'm not afraid of you.
단지 널 잃을까봐 두려워
네가 사라질까봐
I'm only afraid of losing you.
I feel like you're gonna disappear.
얼마나 널 기다렸는지 모를 거야
You don't know how long
I've waited for you.
사자가 양과 사랑에 빠졌네
So the lion fell in love with the lamb.
바보같은 양
What a stupid lamb.
정신나간 사자
What a sick, masochistic lion.
(GENTLE THEME PLAYING)
3가지에 대해서는
확실히 알았다
BELLA: About three things
I was absolutely positive.
첫번째
First,
에드워드는 뱀파이어라는 것
Edward was a vampire.
두번째
Second,
그의 일부분이
there was a part of him,
얼마나 강렬한지는 몰랐지만
and I didn't know
how dominant that part might be,
(HORN HONKS TWICE)
나의 피를 원한다는 것
that thirsted for my blood.
그리고 세번째
And third,
제가 무조건적이고 되돌릴 수
없는 사랑에 빠진 것이다
I was unconditionally and irrevocably
in love with him.
몬테 카를로?
그게 무도회 주제야?
JESSICA: Monte Carlo?
That's our prom theme?
도박, 턱시도 그리고 본드
Gambling, tuxedos, and Bond, James Bond.
(ENGINE PURRS)
오, 세상에나
Oh, my God.
(UP-TEMPO ROCK THEME PLAYING)
이런
Wow.
(CLEARS THROAT)
모두 다 보고 있어
You know, everybody's staring.
저 애는 아니야, 지금 본 거야
Not that guy. No, he just looked.
어차피 나 요즘 막 나가는데
I'm breaking all the rules now anyway.
지옥에 가면 되지
Since I'm going to hell.
꼭 죽어야 되는 거야
So, does a person have to be dying
너처럼 되려면?
to become like you?
아니, 아빠가 이랬어
No, that's just Carlisle.
선택의 여지가 있다면
절대 이렇게 안 하셔
He'd never do this to someone
who had another choice.
이렇게 된 지 얼마나 됐어?
So, how long have you been like this?
1918년부터
Since 1918.
스페인독감으로 죽어갈 때
아빠가 이렇게 했지
That's when Carlisle found me
dying of Spanish influenza.
느낌이 어땠어?
BELLA: What was it like?
(YELLS)
독액은 견디기 힘들었어
EDWARD: The venom was excruciating.
하지만 아빠의 자제가 더 힘든 거지
But what Carlisle did was much harder.
그걸 참아낼 뱀파이어는 많지 않아
Not many of us have the restraint to do that.
그냥 물기만 하면 되잖아?
But didn't he just have to bite?
꼭 그렇진 않아
Not exactly.
우리가 인간의 피를
When we taste
맛보게 되면 광기가 시작돼
human blood, a sort of frenzy begins,
멈추기가 불가능하지
and it's almost impossible to stop.
박사님은 하셨잖아
BELLA: But Carlisle did.
처음엔 나에게
다음에는 부인 에즈메에게
EDWARD: First with me
and then with his wife, Esme.
그럼 박사님 때문에
사람을 안 죽이는 거야?
So is Carlisle the real reason
that you don't kill people?
유일한 이유는 아냐
No, he's not the only reason.
나는 괴물이 되기 싫어
I don't want to be a monster.
우리 가족들은 스스로를
채식주의자라고 생각하지
My family,
we think of ourselves as vegetarians, right,
동물의 피만 먹고 사니까
'cause we only survive
on the blood of animals.
하지만 그건
But it's...
인간이 두부만 먹는 것과 같아
It's like a human only living on tofu.
건강에는 좋지만
만족스럽진 않지
It keeps you strong,
but you're never fully satisfied.
너의 피를 마시는
것과는 다르겠지
It wouldn't be like drinking your blood,
for instance.
웨일런씨를 죽인 게 뱀파이어야?
Was it other vampires that killed Waylon?
그래
Yeah.
다른 놈들도 있어
가끔씩 마주치기도 하지
There are others out there,
and we run into them from time to time.
다른 가족들도 너처럼
마음을 읽어?
Can the rest of your family
read people's minds like you can?
아니, 나만 그래
No. That's just me.
하지만 앨리스는 미래를 봐
But Alice can see the future.
내가 오는 걸 봤겠다
I bet she saw me coming.
앨리스의 환영은 주관적이야
Alice's visions are subjective.
미래는 언제든 바뀔 수 있어
I mean, the future can always change.
(LOUD BANG)
인간처럼 굴어줄래?
이웃이 있다구
Could you act human?
I mean, I've got neighbors.
내일 우리집에 데려갈게
I'm gonna take you to my place tomorrow.
고마워
Thanks.
- 잠깐, 너희 가족이 있는데?
- 그래
- Wait, like, with your family?
- Yeah.
날 안 좋아하면?
What if they don't like me?
뱀파이어 소굴에 가는 게
두려운 게 아니고
So, you're worried not because
you'll be in a house full of vampires,
널 좋아하지 않을까봐
두렵다고?
but because you think
they won't approve of you?
재밌나보지
I'm glad I amuse you.
왜 그래?
What is it?
복잡한데
Complication.
내일 데리러 올게
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
안녕, 아저씨 트럭 보시려구요?
Hey. Come to visit your truck?
좋아보인다, 흙받이 폈네?
Looks good. Got that dent out.
- 그래
- 실은 너희 평면 TV 보려고 왔지
- Yeah.
- Actually, we came to visit your flat-screen.
마리너스의 시즌 첫경기거든
First Mariners game of the season.
그리고 제이콥이 너 보자고
졸라대서 말야
Plus Jacob here keeps bugging me about
seeing you again.
고맙군요, 아빠
Great, Dad. Thanks.
확실하게 살아야지
Just keeping it real, son.
비타민 맥주야
CHARLIE: Vitamin R.
잘 했군
Well done, Chief.
해리의 생선 튀김이야
Harry Clearwater's homemade fish fry.
좋아
Good man.
웨일런 사건은 잘 돼가나?
Any luck with that Waylon case?
동물이 죽인 게
아닌 것 같아
Well, I don't think it was an animal
that killed him.
아닌 줄 알았지
Never thought it was.
인디안 구역에 소문 좀 퍼뜨리게
So spread the word out at the rez, huh?
애들이 숲에 못 들어가게
Keep the kids out of the woods.
그러지
Will do.
아무도 다치길 바라진 않잖아, 그렇지?
Don't want no one else getting hurt, do we?
(SLOW, EXOTIC THEME PLAYING)
(EXHALES)
와
Whoa.
여기 대단하다
This is incredible.
아주 밝고 트여있네
It's so light and open, you know?
뭘 기대했어?
관(棺), 지하 감옥, 성곽?
What did you expect,
coffins and dungeons and moats?
아니, 성곽은 빼고
(CHUCKLES) No, not the moats.
성곽은 아니라고
Not the moats.
여긴 우리가 숨을 필요가 없는 곳이야
This is the one place we don't have to hide.
(OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
이러지 말라고 해놨는데
I told them not to do this.
손잡이 없는 팬에
올리브 오일을 두르세요
MAN ON TV: You add a little bit of olive oil
to a non-stick saute pan,
올리브 오일이 중간온도로
달궈지면 조리를 시작합니다
and you want to cook
with the olive oil in medium-high heat.
저처럼 고기를
자르고 난 다음엔
What I do, I cut this in strips,
and then we gonna cut this...
- 그애 이태리 사람이야?
- 이름이 벨라잖아
- Is she even Italian?
- Her name is Bella.
어쨌든 좋아할 거야
I'm sure she'll love it, no matter what.
음... 냄새 맡아봐
ROSALIE: (SIGHS) Get a whiff of that.
우리집에 인간이 온다!
(SINGSONG) Here comes the human.
벨라, 널 위해 이태리 음식을 만든단다
Bella, we're making Italiano for you.
벨라, 여기는 실질적인
어머니 에즈메
Bella, this is Esme.
My mother for all intents and purposes.
- Bon giorno? (안녕?)
- Molto bene! (잘지내요)
- Bon giorno? - Molto bene!
덕분에 처음으로 부엌을
사용해보는구나
You've given us an excuse
to use the kitchen for the first time.
배고프면 좋겠다
I hope you're hungry.
- 네, 물론이죠!
- 벌써 먹었어요
- Yeah, absolutely.
- She already ate.
잘 됐군!
Perfect.
네, 왜냐하면
여러분은 식사를 안 하시니까요
Yeah, it's just because
I know that you guys don't eat...
사려가 깊네요
Of course. It's very considerate of you.
- 로잘리는 무시해, 나처럼
- 그래
- Just ignore Rosalie. I do.
- ROSALIE: Yeah.
그래요, 이게 모두에게 위험하지
않은 척 하자구요
Let's just keep pretending
like this isn't dangerous for all of us.
절대로 아무 얘기 안 할 거예요
I would never tell anybody anything.
로잘리도 알아
She knows that.
하지만 문제는
너희 둘 사이가 다 알려져서
Yeah, well, the problem is,
you two have gone public now, so...
에밋
Emmett.
아니요, 저애도 알아야 돼요
No, she should know.
얘들이 나쁘게 끝나면 전체
가족이 영향을 받아요
The entire family
will be implicated if this ends badly.
나쁘게 끝난다는 건
Badly, as in...
내가 밥이 되는 거죠
I would become the meal.
(SNICKERING)
(LAUGHING)
안녕, 벨라!
Hi, Bella.
난 앨리스야
I'm Alice.
- 안녕
- Hi.
오, 너 냄새 좋다
You do smell good.
앨리스, 너 뭘?
Alice, what are you...
걱정마, 벨라와 나는
좋은 친구가 될 거야
It's okay.
Bella and I are gonna be great friends.
재스퍼는 최근에
채식주의자가 됐기 때문에
CARLISLE: Sorry,
Jasper's our newest vegetarian.
조금 힘들어해
It's a little difficult for him.
만나서 반가워
It's a pleasure to meet you.
괜찮아, 재스퍼
안 해칠 거야
It's okay, Jasper. You won't hurt her.
좋아요, 벨라에게
집구경 시켜줄게요
All right, I'm gonna take you
on a tour of the rest of the house.
- 그래
- 곧 또 보자
- Okay.
- Well, I'll see you soon.
그래
Okay.
- 귀엽다
- 그러네
- Cute!
- I know.
잘 한 거 같은데
I think that went well.
그거 치워라, 당장
Clean this up. Now.
가족들 행동이 다들 너무 어색했지?
Was that as weird for you as it was for me?
모르겠어
I don't know.
학사모들이야?
Graduation caps?
맞아, 우리끼리의 장난이지
Yeah. It's a private joke.
대학교를 많이 갔거든
We matriculate a lot.
좀 불쌍하다
That's kind of miserable.
고등학교를 반복해서
다녀야하니
I mean, repeating high school
over and over.
그렇긴 하지만, 새로운 곳에서
어린나이로 시작하니까
True, but the younger we start out
in a new place,
한 곳에 더 오래 살 수 있지
the longer we can stay there.
가자
Come on.
여기가 내 방이야
Yeah, this is my room.
(BIRDS CHIRPING OUTSIDE)
침대 없어?
No bed?
없어 난...
No, I don't...
잠을 안 자
I don't sleep.
- 전혀?
- 전혀
- Ever?
- No, not at all.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
그렇구나
Okay.
음악이 아주 많네
Boy, you have so much music.
뭐 듣고 있어?
What are you listening to?
(BUTTON CLICKS)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
드뷔시야
It's Debussy.
- 제목은...
- 응
- I don't know...
- Yeah.
Clair de Lune (달빛)은 정말 좋아
Claire De Lune is great.
- 왜?
- 난 춤 못 춰
- What?
- I can't dance.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
추게 만들 수 있어
Well, I could always make you.
너 무섭지 않아
I'm not scared of you.
그 말은 안 했어야지
Well, you really shouldn't have said that.
(BELLA GASPS)
꽉 잡아야 할 걸, 거미원숭아
You better hold on tight, spider monkey.
(BELLA GIGGLES)
날 믿어?
Do you trust me?
이론상으로
In theory.
그럼 눈 감아
Then close your eyes.
뭐?
What?
이건 진짜가 아냐
(CHUCKLES) This isn't real.
이런 일은 존재하지 않아
This kind of stuff just doesn't exist.
내 세상에는 있어
It does in my world.
(PLAYING GENTLE MELODY)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(SNIFFING)
멈춰
MAN: Hold up.
인간이군
It's human.
아리조나, 어떻게 지내?
Arizona. Yo, what's happening?
너하고 컬린하고?
So you and Cullen, huh?
그거 맘에 안드는데
That's... I don't like it.
내 말은 그애가
I mean, I don't know,
널 잡아먹을 듯이
쳐다보거든
he just looks at you
like you're something to eat.
여기 야채 나왔습니다, 스테파니
Here's your veggie plate, Stephenie.
늦어서 죄송해요, 생물 실습때문에요
Hey, sorry I'm late. Biology project.
너 샐러드 시켰는데
괜찮겠지
I ordered you the spinach salad.
I hope that's okay.
다음엔 아빠도 시켜드세요
You should order one for yourself next time.
스테이크는 줄이시구요
Cut back on the steak.
난 말처럼 튼튼해
Hey, I'm as healthy as a horse.
서장님, 사람들이 알고 싶어해요
Say, Chief, boys want to know,
오늘 퀴츠강에서
뭐 좀 찾으셨어요?
did you find anything
down by Queets River today?
사람의 맨발 자국을 발견했죠
Yeah, we found a bare human footprint,
그게 누구이던지 간에
동쪽을 향하고 있어요
but it looks like whoever that is,
is headed east,
거기선 키셉 보안관이 맡을 거예요
so Kitsap County sheriff is gonna take
over from here.
- 알았어요
- 됐나요?
- CORA: Okay.
- Okay?
빨리 잡기를 바라고 있어요
I just hope they catch him fast.
친구들이 널 부르나본데
Looks like your friends are flagging you.
괜찮으니 가 봐라
It's okay if you wanna go join them.
난 일찍 돌아가야하니
I'm just gonna turn in early anyway.
저두요
Me, too.
벨라, 금요일이야
나가 놀아
Bella, it's Friday night. Go out.
마이크가 너한테 미소를
보내는 거 같구나
Looks like the Newton boy's
got a big smile for you.
네, 좋은 친구예요
Yeah, he's a good buddy.
마을의 얼간이들 중에
What about any of these
other yahoos in town?
관심가는 애는 있니?
Anybody interest you?
남자 얘기 하자구요?
Dad, we gonna talk about boys?
아니라고 봐야지
Yeah, I guess not.
난 널 너무 혼자 두는 거 같아서
I just feel like I leave you alone too much.
사람들하고 어울려야지
You should be around people.
혼자 있어도 괜찮아요
I don't really mind being alone.
그런 면에서 아빠랑 비슷하죠
I guess I'm kind of like my dad in that way.
그래서 야구 일은 어떻게 돼가요?
So, how's all the baseball stuff going?
필은 열심히 하고 있어
Phil's working so hard.
춘계 훈련 말이야
You know, spring training.
일이 확정될지 몰라서
셋집을 알아보고 있어
We're looking for a house to rent
in case things become more permanent.
잭슨빌이 맘에 들거다
You'd like Jacksonville, baby.
그래요?
Yeah?
포크스가 정말 좋아요
I'm really liking Forks.
뭐라구?
What?
포크스에 정이 들어가요
Forks is growing on me.
혹시 남자 때문에 그렇게 된 거니?
Could a guy have anything to do with that?
그래요
Well, yeah.
그럴줄 알았어!
다 얘기해봐, 그 애는 어떠니?
I knew it. Tell me everything.
What is he? Jock? Indie?
똑똑할 것 같은데, 그애 똑똑하니?
I bet he's smart. Is he smart?
엄마 나중에 얘기할게요
Mom, can I talk to you later?
남자 얘기를 해야지!
너 피임은 하니?
Come on, we gotta talk boys.
Are you being safe?
어떻게 들어왔어?
How did you get in here?
창문으로
The window.
자주 그래?
Do you do that a lot?
지난 두 달 동안만
Well, just the past couple of months.
너 자는 모습 보는 게 좋아
I like watching you sleep.
그건 나에겐 매혹적인 일이야
It's kind of fascinating to me.
늘 한가지를 해보고 싶었어
I always want to try one thing.
그대로 가만 있어
Just stay very still.
움직이지마
Don't move.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(BOTH PANTING)
그만!
Stop it!
미안해
I'm sorry.
넌 생각보다 강해
I'm stronger than I thought.
너도 마찬가지야
Yeah. I wish I could say the same.
너에게는 자제력을 잃으면 안 돼
I can't ever lose control with you.
가지마
Hey, don't go.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- 하나 더 가져왔어요
- 고맙다
- Hey, got you another one.
- Thanks.
에드워드 컬린과 데이트해요
I have a date with Edward Cullen.
너보다 나이 들어 보이던데
He's a little old for you, isn't he?
아뇨
No.
그애도 3학년이고 저도 3학년이에요
He's a junior. I'm a junior.
컬린네 좋아하시잖아요
I thought you liked the Cullens.
마을에 있는 남자애들
안 좋아한다면서
I thought you didn't like
any of the boys in town.
에드워드는 마을에 살지 않아요
Edward doesn't live in town.
실제적으로요
Technically.
밖에서 기다려요
He's right outside.
왔다고?
He is?
아빠를 만나겠대요, 공식적으로요
Yeah, he wanted to meet you, officially.
알았다, 들여 보내
All right. Bring him in.
잘 대해주세요
Could you be nice?
그애는 중요해요
He's important.
스완 서장님
Chief Swan.
정식으로 인사드립니다
에드워드 컬린입니다.
I want to formally introduce myself.
I'm Edward Cullen.
반갑네, 에드워드
Hi, Edward.
벨라는 늦지 않을 겁니다
Bella won't be out too late tonight.
저희 가족과 야구를
할 거거든요
She's just gonna play baseball
with my family.
야구라고?
Baseball?
네, 그럴 계획입니다
Yes, sir, that's the plan.
벨라가 야구를 한다고?
(CHUCKLES) Bella's gonna play baseball.
행운을 비네
Well, good luck with that.
잘 돌보겠습니다
약속드리죠
I'll take good care of her. I promise.
벨라
Hey.
호신용 스프레이 갖고 있지?
Still got that pepper spray?
네, 아빠
(WHISPERS) Yeah, Dad.
언제부터 뱀파이어가 야구를 좋아했어?
And since when do vampires like baseball?
미국의 역사이기도 하고
Well, it's the American pastime,
또 폭풍우가 다가올 때만
and there's a thunderstorm coming.
경기를 할 수 있어
이유는 알게 될 거야
It's the only time we can play.
You'll see why.
벨라
Hey.
와줘서 기쁘다, 심판이 필요했거든
Glad you're here. We need an umpire.
우리가 속인다고 생각하셔
She thinks we cheat.
속이는 거 알아
I know you cheat.
- 네가 본대로 판정해라, 벨라
- 알았어요
- Call them as you see them, Bella.
- Okay.
(SUPERMASSIVE BLACK HOLE PLAYING)
시간이 됐네
It's time.
(THUNDER CRACKS)
왜 천둥이 필요한지 알겠어요
Okay, now I see why you need the thunder.
홈런이 되겠죠?
That's gotta be a home run, right?
에드워드는 아주 빨라
Edward's very fast.
Ooh, baby,
don't you know I suffer?
(SINGING) Ooh, baby,
Ooh, baby, I'm a fool for you
빨리! 로잘리
Come home, Rosalie!
- 아웃이야
- 아웃!
- You're out.
- Out!
뭘 그래, 그냥 게임이잖아
Babe, come on. It's just a game.
You set my soul alight
잘했다
Nice kitty.
Ooh
You set my soul alight
뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
Super massive black hole
원숭이 남친이야
My monkey man.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
멈춰!
Stop!
(OMINOUS ROCK THEME PLAYING)
오고 있어, 우리 소리를 들었을 거야
They were leaving. Then they heard us.
- 가자
- 이미 늦었어
- Let's go.
- It's too late.
머리를 내려
Get your hair down.
도움이 안돼
건너편에서도 냄새를 맡겠는데
Like that'll help.
I can smell her from across the field.
데려오는 게 아닌데
정말 미안해
I shouldn't have brought you here.
I'm so sorry.
- 뭐?
- 말하지 말고 내 뒤에 서
- What? What are you...
- Just be quiet and stand behind me.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
당신들 공 같군요
I believe this belongs to you.
고마워요
Thank you.
난 로렌트예요
I am Laurent.
여기는 빅토리아예요
And this is Victoria
그리고 제임스
and James.
난 칼라일이고 우리 가족이에요
I'm Carlisle. This is my family.
안녕하세요
Hello.
당신들의 사냥 활동이
우리에게 문제를 일으켰어요
I'm afraid your hunting activities
have caused something of a mess for us.
사과드리죠
Our apologies.
구역이 있는지 몰랐어요
We didn't realize the territory
had been claimed.
그래요, 우리는 근처에
집을 갖고 있어요
Yes, well, we maintain
a permanent residence nearby.
정말인가요?
Really?
더 이상 문제되지 않을 거예요
Well, we won't be a problem anymore.
그냥 지나가는 길이니까
We were just passing through.
인간들이 추적중이지만
동쪽으로 따돌렸어요
The humans were tracking us,
but we led them east.
안전할 거예요
You should be safe.
잘 됐군요
Excellent.
그럼
So,
우리 셋이 같이 해도 되나요?
could you use three more players?
어때요, 그냥 한 게임만요
Come on. Just one game.
그럼요, 못할 거 없죠
Sure. Why not?
몇 명은 갈 거니까
대신 뛰면 돼요
A few of us were leaving.
You could take their place.
우리가 공격하죠
We'll bat first.
내 커브볼은 환상적이죠
I'm the one with the wicked curveball.
그 정도는 처리할 수 있겠는 걸요
Well, I think we can handle that.
두고 보죠
We shall see.
(OMINOUS THEME PLAYS)
(WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY)
(SNIFFING)
간식을 가져왔군
You brought a snack.
(SNARLING)
인간이라고?
LAURENT: A human?
저 애는 우리와 왔어요
CARLISLE: The girl is with us.
당신들이 가는 게 좋겠어요
I think it best if you leave.
시합이 끝난 거 같군요
I can see the game is over.
지금 가죠
We'll go now.
제임스
James.
벨라를 데려고 나가
CARLISLE: Get Bella out of here.
어서 가
Go.
됐어! 내가 할게! 괜찮아!
Okay, I've got it! I've got it! I'm all right!
왜 나를 잡으러 오는 거야?
What, now he's coming after me?
잘들어, 제임스는 추적자야
사냥에 집착해
Listen to me. James is a tracker.
The hunt is his obsession.
그의 마음을 읽었어
아까 내 반응 때문에 열이 올랐어
I read his mind.
My reaction on the field set him off.
내가 아주 신나는 게임을 만든 셈이지
I just made this his most exciting game ever.
- 그는 멈추지 않아!
- 어떻게 하지?
- He's never gonna stop.
- What should we do?
그를 죽여야돼
갈기갈기 찢어서 불태워야해
We have to kill him.
Rip him apart and burn the pieces.
- 어딜 가는 거야?
- 포크스에서 멀리
- Where we going?
- Away from Forks.
- 밴쿠버로 가든가
- 난 집에 가야해, 당장
- We'll get a ferry to Vancouver.
- I have to go home. Now.
- 데려다줘
- 집에 가면 안 돼
- You have to take me home.
- You can't go home.
너의 냄새를 쫒아서
제일 먼저 찾아 갈거야
He's just gonna trace your scent there.
It's the first place he's gonna look.
- 아빠가 계시는데
- 상관없어!
- But my dad is there. We...
- It doesn't matter!
상관있지!
우리 때문에 당하실텐데
Yes, it does!
He could get killed because of us!
너를 먼저 내보낼 수 있게 해줘, 알겠어?
Just let me get you out of here first,
all right?
우리 아빠야! 돌아가야돼!
It's my dad! We have to go back!
추격을 따돌릴 수 있는 방법을
어떻게든 찾을 수 있을거야
We'll figure a way
to lead the tracker away somehow.
잘은 모르겠지만 뭔가는 해야지
I don't know. But we have to do something.
(SPORTS PLAYING ON TV)
- 에드워드, 날 내버려둬!
- 벨라, 제발 이러지마
- Edward, I said leave me alone.
- Bella, don't do this, please.
다 끝났어! 나가!
It's over! Get out!
얘야, 벨라
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
벨라, 무슨 일이냐?
Bella? What's going on?
여기서 나가야돼요, 지금 떠나요
I just gotta get out of here. I'm leaving now.
에드워드
Hey.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
벨라?
CHARLIE: Bella?
뭐라고 하지?
What am I gonna say to him?
상처드릴 수 없어
I can't hurt him.
- 무슨 일이냐?
- 해야만 돼
- Bella, what's going on?
- You just have to.
트럭으로 와
I'll be down at the truck.
그애가 해쳤니?
Did he hurt you?
아뇨
No.
헤어지자던?
Break up with you or something?
아뇨, 내가 찼어요
No, I broke up with him.
좋아한다면서?
I thought you liked him.
그래서 떠나는 거예요
Yeah, that's why I have to leave.
이런 건 싫어요, 집에 가야겠어요
I don't want this. I have to go home.
집?
Home? Your...
피닉스에 엄마도 없잖아
CHARLIE: Your mom's not even in Phoenix.
돌아오실 거예요
가면서 전화하죠
BELLA: She'll come home.
I'll call her from the road.
지금 운전해가면 안 되지
You're not gonna drive home right now.
자면서 생각해봐라
아침에도 가야겠다면
You can sleep on it.
If you still feel like going in the morning,
- 공항에 태워주마
- 아뇨, 운전하고 싶어요
- I'll take you to the airport.
- No. I want to drive.
운전하면 생각할 시간이 많이 생기겠죠
It'll give me more time to think.
피곤해지면 모텔에서
쉴게요, 약속해요
I mean, if I get really tired,
I'll pull into a motel. I promise.
벨라, 네 곁에 많이
있어주진 못했다만
Look, Bella, I know I'm not
that much fun to be around,
바뀔 수 있을 거야
함께 시간도 보내고
but I can change that.
We can do more stuff together.
어떻게요?
Like what?
뭘 하면서요? TV로 야구보는 거요?
Like watch baseball on the flat-screen?
매일 저녁 식당에서
밥 먹구요?
Eat at the diner every night?
Steak and cobbler?
그건 아빠 생활이지 난 아니예요
Dad, that's you. That's not me.
벨라, 이러지 마라
Bella, come on, I just...
이제야 겨우 만났는데
I just got you back.
지금 나가지 않으면
Yeah, and, you know, if I don't get out now,
엄마처럼 여기 쳐박히게 될 거예요
then I'm just gonna be stuck here like Mom.
(DOOR SLAMS)
아버지는 용서하실 거야
Your father's gonna forgive you.
내가 운전해줄게
Why don't you let me drive?
용서 안 하실 거야
He won't.
아빠 얼굴을 봤어야해
You should've seen his face.
엄마가 했던 말을 아빠에게 했어
I told him the same thing
that my mom told him
엄마가 아빠를 떠나면서 했던 말
when she was leaving him.
네가 떠날 수 있는 유일한 방법이야
It's the only way he'd let you go.
걱정마, 이젠 안전하셔
우리를 추적하니까
Just don't worry about him now.
He's safe. The tracker's following us.
(LOUD BANG)
(GASPS)
- 뭐야?
- 에멧이야
- Oh, God.
- It's just Emmett.
앨리스가 뒷차에 있어
Alice is in the car behind us.
(MELANCHOLY THEME PLAYING)
기다려!
CARLISLE: Wait.
제임스에 대해 경고해주러 왔어
He came to warn us about James.
이건 내 싸움이 아니예요
난 이런 게임에 질렸어요
This isn't my fight,
and I've grown tired of his games,
하지만 그는 치명적인
감지 감각을 가졌어요
but he's got unparalleled senses,
absolutely lethal.
300년 동안 그런 건
보지 못 했어요
I've never seen anything like him
in my 300 years.
빅토리아라는 여자
얕보지 말아요
And the woman, Victoria,
don't underestimate her.
그런 놈과 싸워봤어
I've had to fight our kind before.
- 죽이기가 쉽지 않아
- 불가능 하진 않지
- They're not easy to kill.
- EMMETT: But not impossible.
찢어 죽여서 불 태우자고
We'll tear them apart and burn the pieces.
누굴 죽이는 생각은
하면 안 되는데
I don't relish the thought
of killing another creature,
제임스 같이 잔인하더라도
even a sadistic one like James.
- 놈이 우리를 먼저 죽이면요?
- 벨라와 남쪽으로 갈게요
- What if he kills one of us first?
- I'm gonna run Bella south.
추적자를 유인해 주실래요?
Can you lead the tracker away from here?
안돼, 에드워드
놈은 네가 벨라와 있을 걸 알거야
No, Edward.
James knows you would never leave Bella.
- 너를 쫒을 거다
- 내가 벨라와 가지
- He'll follow you.
- ALICE: I'll go with Bella.
재스퍼와 남쪽으로 갈게
Jasper and I will drive her south.
안전하게 지킬 거야, 에드워드
I'll keep her safe, Edward.
- 네 생각을 감출 수 있겠어?
- 그래
- Can you keep your thoughts to yourself?
- Yes.
로잘리, 어머니
Rosalie, Esme,
이걸 입어요
추적자가 냄새를 쫒아오도록
could you put these on
so the tracker will pick up Bella's scent?
왜? 저애가 뭔데?
Why? What is she to me?
로잘리, 에드워드 친구잖아
Rosalie, Bella is with Edward.
이젠 우리 가족이야
She's part of this family now,
우리는 가족을 지키잖아
and we protect our family.
오, 세상에 만약
Oh, God. If anything...
만약
What if...
무슨 일이 생기면 맹세컨데
If anything happens, I swear to God...
아무일 없을 거야
Nothing's gonna happen.
우리는 일곱이고
저들은 둘이야
There's seven of us,
and there's two of them,
모든 일이 끝나면
데리러 갈게
and when everything's done,
I'm gonna come back and get you.
알았어
Yeah.
벨라, 넌 이제 내 생명이야
Bella, you are my life now.
(ENGINES STARTING)
엄마, 또 저예요
Hey, Mom. It's me again.
전화기가 꺼졌나보네요
You must have let your phone die
or something.
저 포크스에 없지만 문제는 없어요
나중에 설명 드릴게요
I'm not in Forks, but everything's okay,
and I'll explain it later.
로잘리, 나무에 문질러
EDWARD: Rosalie, mark the tree.
됐어
That's good.
(GROWLS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(GASPS)
왜 그래? 뭐가 보여?
What is it? What do you see?
(LOW RUMBLING)
(FIERCE GROWLING)
놈이 눈치챘어
He's figured it out.
추적자가 방향을 바꿨어
The tracker, he just changed course.
- 어디로 가고 있지? 앨리스
- 거울들
- Where will it take him, Alice?
- Mirrors.
방 안 가득 거울이 있어
A room full of mirrors.
에드워드는 환영이
늘 정확하진 않다던데
Edward said the visions
weren't always certain.
앨리스는 사람들이 마음의 방향을 정하면
그 후 일어날 일을 보는 거야
JASPER: She sees the course people
are on while they're on it.
사람들이 마음을 바꾸게 되면
환영도 바뀌지
If they change their minds,
the vision changes.
알았어, 그러면 추적자의 마음의 방향이
Okay, so the course that
the tracker's on now
발레 연습실로 이끄는 거야?
is gonna lead him to a ballet studio?
- 여기 가봤어?
- 어릴 때 교습을 받았어
- You've been here?
- I took lessons as a kid.
다녔던 학교에 저런
문틀이 있었어
The school I went to
had an arch just like that.
학교가 여기 피닉스에 있어?
Was your school here in Phoenix?
그래
Yeah.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
- 에드워드, 괜찮아?
- 추적자를 놓쳤어
- Edward, are you okay?
- We've lost the tracker.
여자는 아직 이 부근에 있고
The woman's still in the area.
로잘리와 어머니는 네
아버지를 보호하러 갔고
Rosalie and Esme are going back
to Forks to protect your father.
데리러 갈게
너와 나는 어딘가로 가자, 둘이서
I'm coming to get you. Then you and I
are gonna go somewhere alone.
가족들은 계속 찾아다닐 거야
And the others will keep hunting.
널 안전하게 하기 위해
무슨 일이든 할 거야
I'll do whatever it takes
to make you safe again.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
집
엄마, 메세지 받으셨네요
Hey, Mom, I'm glad you got my message.
집에서 뭐 하세요?
What are you doing home?
벨라! 벨라! 벨라! 어디 있니?
Bella? Bella? Bella, where are you?
- 진정하세요, 별일 없어요
- 벨라! 벨라!
- Calm down, everything's fine.
- Bella? Bella?
나중에 다 설명 드릴게요
I'll explain everything later.
엄마? 듣고 계세요?
Mom, are you there?
포크스 고등학교는 학생
신상정보 보호에 약하군
JAMES: Forks High School doesn't protect
its students' privacy very well.
빅토리아가 네 이전 주소를
찾는 게 너무 쉬웠어
It was just too easy for Victoria
to find your previous address.
여기 집이 좋은데
It's a nice house you have here.
너를 기다릴 준비를 하는데
I was prepared to wait for you,
걱정하는 아빠의 전화를
받고 엄마가 집에 오셨지
but then Mom came home after she received
a very worried call from your dad,
일이 아주 잘 풀렸어
and it all worked out quite well.
잠깐만, 기다려요
RENEE: Wait, wait...
엄마, 건들지마!
Don't touch her! Don't...
- 아직 구할 수 있어
- 그냥 두라고
- You can still save her.
- BELLA: Don't!
하지만 친구들과
떨어져야지
But you're gonna have to get away
from your friends.
- 그럴 수 있겠어?
- 어디서 만날까?
- Can you handle that?
- Where should I meet you?
옛날 발레 연습실 어때?
How about your old ballet studio?
만약 누구를 데려온다면
And I'll know if you bring anyone along.
불쌍한 엄마가 대가를
치르게 될 거야
Poor Mommy would
pay the price for that mistake.
난 어떻게 죽을지 생각해
본 적은 없었지만
BELLA: I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
사랑하는 사람이 있는 곳에서
죽는 것은 괜찮은 방법같다
But dying in the place of someone I love
seems like a good way to go.
죽음과 맞서기로 한 결정을
후회할 수는 없다
I can't bring myself to regret the decisions
that brought me face-to-face with death.
그 결정으로 에드워드를 만났으니까
They also brought me to Edward.
벨라! 벨라! 벨라! 어디 있니?
RENEE: Bella? Bella? Bella, where are you?
- 엄마?
- 벨라?
- Mom?
- Bella?
- 엄마?
- 여기 있었구나
- Mom?
- There you are.
뭐하고 있니?
RENEE: What are you doing in here?
모두들 날 놀려요
YOUNG BELLA: Everyone makes fun of me.
괜찮아, 넌 춤을 잘 춰
Come on, you're a wonderful dancer.
엄마, 난 형편없어요
Mom, I suck.
(JAMES LAUGHING)
넌 형편없지 않아
You do not suck.
내가 좋아하는 부분이지
That's my favorite part.
넌 고집센 아이였지?
You were a stubborn child, weren't you?
- 엄마는 없잖아
- 없지
- She's not even here.
- No.
미안
JAMES: Sorry.
네가 쉽게 만들어줬어
You know, but you really made it too easy.
그럼, 더 재미있게 하기위해
So to make things more entertaining,
함께 지내는 영화를
만들어볼까
I'm gonna make a little film
of our time together.
너희 집에서 가져왔는데
괜찮겠지
I borrowed this from your house.
I hope you don't mind.
좋아
Good.
준비
And
액션!
action.
에드워드 마음 아프겠는 걸
That'll break Edward's little heart.
절대로 에드워드는 상관없어!
You have...
Edward has nothing to do with this!
하지만 상관할걸
But he does.
그의 분노로 더 재밌는 시합이 되겠는 걸
His rage will make for more interesting sport
너를 보호하려고 할테니까
than his feeble attempt to protect you.
계속하자구
And let's continue.
(GROWLS)
(WHOOSHING)
(BELLA YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
예술이네, 아주 역동적인 영상이야
Beautiful. Very visually dynamic.
난 무대를 잘 골라
I chose my stage well.
놈이 널 변화시킬 의지력이
없던 게 유감이군
It's too bad he didn't have
the strength to turn you.
대신 연약한 인간으로
놔두다니
Instead, he kept you
this fragile little human.
사실은 잔인한 거지
It's cruel, really.
(SCREAMS)
에드워드에게 얼마나 아픈지 말해
Tell Edward how much it hurts.
복수해달라고 해, 말하라고!
Tell him to avenge you. Tell him!
- 안 돼! 에드워드
- 말해! 말하라고!
- No, Edward, don't!
- Tell him! Tell him!
(YELLING)
(PANTS)
(JAMES GROWLING)
혼자인가 보군
다른 놈들보다 빠르군
You're alone
'cause you're faster than the others.
하지만 강하진 못 해
But not stronger.
널 죽일만큼 강해
I'm strong enough to kill you.
(YELLS)
미안해
I'm sorry.
(JAMES GRUNTS)
(BELLA SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(BELLA GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(BOTH GROWLING)
(YELLING)
(RAPID GASPING)
벨라! 벨라! 괜찮아
Bella, Bella, it's okay.
얘야, 그만 됐다
Son. Enough.
네가 누군지 기억해라
Remember who you are.
(BELLA YELLING)
벨라, 안심해
ALICE: Bella, you're okay.
벨라는 네 도움이 필요해
Bella needs you.
괜찮아
It's okay.
맙소사
Oh, God.
아빠, 피예요
Carlisle? Her blood.
- 형제들이 놈을 처리할 거야
- 내가 잡았어
- Your brothers will take care of him.
- I got him.
- 아빠!
- 불을 피워
- ALICE: Carlisle!
- Start the fire.
마루판을 가져와
EMMETT: Get the floorboards.
- 앨리스!
- 앨리스, 가봐
- JASPER: Alice!
- Alice, go.
혈관을 심하게 다쳤다
피를 너무 많이 흘렸어
Her femoral artery's been severed.
She's losing too much blood.
아니, 머리가 타오르는 것 같아
No, no, my head is burning!
독액이에요
It's the venom.
변화를 막을 건지
결정을 해야돼
You have to make a choice.
You could let the change happen.
아뇨
No.
안돼요
- 변할 거야, 에드워드, 전에 봤던 일이야
- 꼭 그럴 필요는 없다
- It's gonna happen, Edward. I've seen it.
- It doesn't have to be that way.
아직은 자신의 피가 많아
앨리스, 벨트로 지혈대를 만들어줘
She's still hemorrhaging.
Alice, make me a tourniquet. Your belt.
아버지, 다른 방법은요?
Carlisle, what's my other option?
(GASPING)
내 손 위쪽을 묶어
Tie it above my hands.
아버지!
Carlisle!
가거라
Go.
- 독액은 빨아낼 수 있다
- 아뇨, 전 멈추지 못 해요
- We could try to suck the venom out.
- You know I won't be able to stop.
멈추려는 의지를 가져
Then find the will to stop.
너의 선택이야
But choose.
시간이 얼마 없어
She only has minutes left.
안 아프게 해줄게, 벨라
I'm gonna make it go away, Bella.
(GASPING)
안 아프게 해줄게
I'm gonna make it go away.
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
(EDWARD GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
에드워드, 그만!
피는 깨끗해, 네가 죽이겠다
Edward, stop.
Her blood is clean. You're killing her.
에드워드
Edward.
그만!
Stop.
멈춰!
(SOFTLY) Stop.
의지를 찾아
Find the will.
(BLUESY POP BALLAD PLAYING)
죽음은 평화롭고 쉽다
BELLA: Death is peaceful, easy.
삶이 더 힘들다
Life is harder.
벨라?
Bella?
아가야?
Baby?
벨라
(WHISPERS) Bella.
- 엄마?
- 그래
- Mom?
- Hey.
그애 어디 있어요?
Where is he?
에드워드
Where's...
에드워드 어딨죠?
Where's Edward?
자고 있다
He's asleep.
떠나질 않더구나
He never leaves.
아빠는 식당에 가셨고
And your dad, he's down at the cafeteria.
어떻게 된 거예요?
What happened?
네가 떨어져서 다리가 부러졌어
Well, when you fell, you broke your leg,
피를 많이 흘렸고
and you lost a lot of blood.
아무것도 기억 안 나는구나?
You don't remember any of this, do you?
에드워드가 박사님과 여기 왔어
Edward came down with his dad
포크스로 돌아가자고
널 설득하려고
to try to convince you
to come back to Forks.
네가 그 호텔로 갔다가
넘어지면서
So you went over to their hotel,
then you tripped,
계단을 두 개나 굴렀고
and you fell down two flights of stairs.
창문을 뚫고 나갔어
Went through a window.
제가 그렇죠
Yeah, that sounds like me.
아가, 안 됐구나
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
필이네
It's Phil.
필이 네 걱정 많이 했단다
He's so worried about you.
문자도 하시네요?
You're texting.
드디어 하지
(CHUCKLES) Finally, yeah.
플로리다에 머물고 있어
I told him to stay down in Florida.
얘야, 잭슨빌이 맘에 들거야
매일 화창하단다
Honey, you are gonna love Jacksonville.
It's sunny every day,
귀엽고 작은 집을 구했고
너만의 화장실을 갖을 수 있단다
and we found the cutest little house,
and you've got your own bathroom.
엄마, 포크스에 살고 싶어요
Mom, I still want to live in Forks.
뭐?
What?
포크스에 살고 싶다구요
I want to live in Forks.
벨라, 알았다, 얘기해보자구나
Well, okay, but we'll talk about it.
아빠 좀 불러주실래요?
Do you mind getting Dad?
드릴 말씀이 있어요, 사과드려야돼요
I have to talk to him. Apologize.
알았다, 얘야, 모셔 올게
Okay, baby. I'll go get him.
- 그리고 간호사 불러올게
- 네
- And I'll go get a nurse, okay?
- Okay.
어떻게 됐어?
So what happened?
제임스는?
Where's James?
우리가 처리했어
We took care of it.
빅토리아는 달아났고
And the woman, Victoria, she ran off.
네 덕분에 살았어
I'm alive because of you.
아니, 나 때문에 이렇게 된 거야
No, you're in here because of me.
더 나쁜 건
The worst part of it was that
멈추지 못할 줄 알았어
I thought I wasn't gonna be able to stop.
멈췄잖아
You did stop.
벨라, 잭슨빌로 가
내가 더 상처주지 않게
Bella, you gotta go to Jacksonville
so I can't hurt you anymore.
뭐?
What?
너 정말, 안 돼!
Are you... No!
싫어!
No!
어떻게, 무슨 말인지 모르겠어
I don't even know what you're... How...
나보고 떠나라고
말하고 있는 거야?
What are you talking about?
You want me to go away? I can't...
아니, 널 떠날 순 없어
No, I can't... I can't just leave you...
알아
I know.
우린 헤어질 수 없어
We can't be apart.
넌 날 못 떠나
You can't leave me.
나 여기 있어
I'm here.
알았으니까 그런 말 하지마
Okay, just don't...
절대로 그런 말하면 안돼
You just can't say stuff like that to me. Ever.
내가 어디 갈 데가 있겠어?
Where else am I gonna go?
(GENTLE THEME PLAYING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
앨리스가 드레스 빌려줬어
Alice lent me the dress.
기브스는...
The cast is...
완벽해
You're perfect.
제가 돌보겠습니다, 스완 서장님
I'll take care of her, Chief Swan.
전에도 들은 소리군
I've heard that before.
좋아, 벨라
All right, Bells.
호신용 스프레이 백에 넣어놨다
I put a new can of pepper spray in your bag.
아빠
Dad.
그리고
And...
너 예쁘구나
Well, you look beautiful.
고마워요
Thanks.
갈게요
See you.
금방 돌아올게
Hey. I'll be right back.
- 벨라
- 제이콥
- Bella.
- Jacob.
안녕
Hey.
- 멋진데
- 너도 그래
- Nice.
- You, too.
무도회 가려고?
파트너랑 왔어?
Are you crashing the prom or something?
Did you come with a date?
아니
No.
우리 아빠가 너한테 얘기하라고 돈 주셨어
My dad paid me to come talk to you.
20달러
(CHUCKLES) Twenty bucks.
얘기해봐
Let's hear it.
화내지마, 알았지?
Just don't get mad, okay?
남자친구와 헤어지라셔
He wants you to break up
with your boyfriend.
그게 아빠 말씀을 인용하자면,
It's just, he said, quote,
"우리가 지켜본다"
''We'll be watching you.''
(LAUGHS)
- 알았어, 고맙다고 전해드려
- 그래
- Okay, well, tell him, ''Thanks.''
- Okay.
- 돈 벌었네
- 그렇군, 내가 도와줄게
- And to pay up.
- Okay. Let me help you.
제이콥
Jacob.
내가 데려가지
I'll take it from here.
그럼 또 보자, 벨라
Guess I'll see you around, Bella.
그래
All right.
혼자 2분 놔뒀더니
늑대의 후예하고?
I leave you alone for two minutes,
and the wolves descend.
- 이런 걸 나한테 시키다니
- 웃어
- I can't believe you're making me do this.
- Just smile.
Tonight! Lightning Strikes!
Don't go stay tonight!
이런, 날 죽이려고 작정했구나
Wow. You are really trying to kill me.
무도회는 중요한 과정이야
네가 놓치는 걸 바라지 않아
The prom is an important rite of passage.
I didn't want you to miss anything.
이런
Oh.
(ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
Everyday we're going all the way
Everyday, everyday, everyday
we're going all the way
Tonight! Lightning Strikes!
벨라! 여기야
Bella, hey!
- 가고 싶어?
- 그래
- Do you want to go?
- Yeah.
좋아요, 속도를 줄여 볼까요
DJ: All right, slowing it down.
(APPLAUSE)
추실까요?
Shall we?
진심이야?
You're serious?
왜 아니겠어?
Why not.
Wide on my plastic toys
(SINGING) Wide on my plastic toys
Then when the cops closed the fair
I cut my long baby hair
Stole me a dog-eared map
봐, 너 춤추잖아
See, you're dancing.
무도회에서
At prom.
Have I found you
Flightless bird
Jealous
Weeping
에드워드, 왜 날 구했어?
Edward, why did you save me?
독액이 퍼지게 놔뒀다면
If you just let the venom spread,
지금쯤은 너와 같았을텐데
I could be like you by now.
넌 그 말이 뭔지 몰라
You don't know what you're saying.
- 넌 이걸 원하지 않아
- 너를 원해
- You don't want this.
- I want you.
항상
Always.
네 생명을 끝내지 않을 거야
I'm not gonna end your life for you.
난 이미 죽어가고 있어
I'm dying already.
매순간 가까워져
Every second, I get closer.
나이가 드니까
Older.
원래 그래야 하는 거야
That's the way it's supposed to be.
앨리스는 내가 너처럼 된 걸 봤대
Alice said that she saw me like you.
- 직접 들었어
- 그애 환영은 변해
- I heard her.
- Her visions change.
사람들의 결정에 따라 변하지
Yeah, based on what people decide.
난 결정했어
I've decided.
그걸 꿈꾸는 거야?
So that's what you dream about.
괴물이 되는 거?
Becoming a monster.
내 꿈은 너와 영원히 함께하는 거야
I dream about being with you forever.
영원히
Forever?
지금 준비됐어?
And you're ready right now?
그래
Yes.
Bleeding or lost you
American mouth
Big pill
그 정도로는 안 돼
그냥 나와 오래 행복하게 살자
Is it not enough
just to have a long and happy life with me?
알았어
Yeah.
지금은
For now.
오늘밤 변하게 될 사람은 없다
BELLA: No one will surrender tonight,
하지만 포기하지 않을 것이다
but I won't give in.
내가 원하는 걸 아니까
I know what I want.
Have I found you
Flightless bird
Grounded
Bleeding or lost you
American mouth
How come I end up where I started
How come I end up where I went wrong
Won't take my eyes off the ball again
You reel me out then you cut the string
How come I end up where I started
How come I end up where I went wrong
Won't take my eyes off the ball again
First you reel me out
and then you cut the string
You used to be all right
What happened?
Did the cat get your tongue
Did your string come undone
One by one
It comes to us all
It's as soft as your pillow
I dreamed I was missing
You were so scared
But no one would listen
'Cause no one else cared
After my dreaming
I woke with this fear
What am I leaving
When I'm done here?
So if you're asking me
I want you to know
When my time comes
Forget the wrong that I've done
Help me leave behind some
Reasons to be missed
Don't resent me
And when you're feeling empty
Keep me in your memory
Leave out all the rest
Forgetting all the hurt inside
You've learned to hide so well
Pretending someone else can come
And save me from myself
I can't be who you are
When my time comes
Forget the wrong that I've done
Help me leave behind some
Reasons to be missed
Don't resent me
And when you're feeling empty
Keep me in your memory
Leave out all the rest
Forgetting all the hurt inside
You've learned to hide so well
Pretending someone else can come
And save me from myself
I can't be who you are
How can I decide what's right
When you're clouding up my mind
I can't win your losing fight
All the time
How can I ever own what's mine
When you're always taking sides
But you won't take away my pride
No, not this time
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
But how did we get here?
I think I know
The truth is hiding in your eyes
And its hanging on your tongue
Just boiling in my blood
But you think that I can't see
What kind of man that you are
If you're a man at all
Well, I will figure this one out on my own
I'm screaming I love you so
My thoughts you can't decode
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
Yeah
But how did we get here?
Well, I think I know how
Do you see what we've done
We're gonna make such fools of ourselves
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
Yeah, yeah, yeah
How did we get here?
When I used to know you so well
I think I know
There is something I see in you
It might kill me
I want it to be true